Heat. Heat.
Heat. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Welcome living mana church family. It's
so good to see you guys here today on
this Sabbath, this very for a big chunk
of the country, a cold wintry Sabbath
with either snow or icy rain or just
extremely cold weather. But we are happy
that you are here with Living Mana
Church and inside and warm by God's
grace. We are just so thankful that you
are here and that we can worship
together. For for some of you, you're
going to be just maybe tuning in for the
first time because your church may have
closed its doors because uh of the
weather. And I just want you to know
we're here online international church
um all the time. So we're here whether
the weather is good or the weather is
bad. So you are welcome to visit us
whenever um the the spirit moves you. I
was sharing with one of our members who
text me this morning
>> saying jokingly saying church be
cancelled today because of the weather
outside
roads are pretty icy
>> a lot of people
>> that's funny roads are
>> um we want to let you guys
that uh today's
um Sabbath school uh you all need to
just start inviting people.
>> Yes.
>> You know, we typically say
um Sabbath school
will be uh we typically, you know, let
>> sermons coming. Yeah. Make sure you
invite the people. And we do it for
Sabbath school as well,
>> but we're doing it in a in a special way
for Sabbath school.
>> Yes.
Okay. Um, testing. So, do we do you
Okay, put put a one in the chat. Okay,
we see two.
Okay. Sound is off for for pastor. All
right. So, let's work on that. Our
pastor mic is low.
>> All right. So, if you can hear pastor.
Okay. No sound from pastor. Okay. Put a
one in the chat if you can hear me. And
put um and Okay. Okay. They just can't
hear you. So, we have to work on your
mic because you must be heard.
>> I must be heard.
>> And while we're working on that, let let
me welcome Please put a
please put a one. We have people from
all over.
>> And you know what? We're going to do
something a little bit different real
quick. I'm just going to borrow this
real quick and just say what I just
said.
>> The main interruption.
>> That's right. There you go. I've taken
her mic. taking my
>> um so what I was saying was we
typically, you know, let people know,
hey, the sermon's about to start. Make
sure you invite people uh
make sure you invite
people
to the Sabbath, I mean to the divine
service. Um, we also do this for Sabbath
school, but in a special way, we're
doing this for Sabbath school
>> today because today's Sabbath school is
going to be fire.
>> Okay,
>> even though
>> it's cold.
>> We're It's cold and we're going to be
talking about
>> cold.
>> We are looking for the fire for sure.
Want you guys You guys have been putting
where you are viewing from. We have Oh
my goodness. I've seen New York City, Ro
and other parts of um Rochester, other
parts of New York. Rochester, New York.
I've seen uh I think Lach, Texas, where
they said it was very cold. I'm just
going back. Welcome from Arkansas. Good
to see you here.
Please put in the chat where you're
viewing from. And if this is your very
first time, please put a one in the
chat. Um I just saw somebody say from
Oklahoma City and it's freezing there.
Uh, all right. Okay. East Europe,
Serbia, welcome. I think I've welcomed
you before. So, good to have you coming
back and and here at Living Mana Church.
Uh, let's see. Please put a one in the
chat if this is your first time.
Northwest Arkansas, welcome. Good to see
you and to have you here with us. Uh,
happy Sabbath from New Jersey. Good to
see you. Welcome to Living Mana Church.
All right, we have a one and it looks
like this is Frederick. Um, welcome
>> Frederick the Great.
>> Frederick the Great. All right. Well,
welcome to Living Mana Church. We are a
100% online 7th Day Adventist Church.
We're with the Northeastern Conference
and we have we're not just here on
Sabbath. We're here all throughout the
week. We have Mental Health Monday which
we have a new episode for mental health
Monday. Dr. White and myself will be
going live. We have True Health Tuesday
uh where we talk about health. two
prayer services. We are just so happy to
have you here and I'll be telling you
more about this when the divine worship
service starts. So everyone any every
anyone that's a one and here for the
first time definitely stay tuned in so
you can hear all about living mana
church. Okay, welcome u from Lancaster,
California.
I uh have family in Lancaster,
California. Grew up going there as a
little girl. Okay, brother Tennessee,
always good to see you. He says it's
freezing though. Yes, it is freezing
here in the south. Freezing here in
Alabama as well. Compton, California,
welcome. Good to see you.
Warsaw, uh, New York, good to um from
Yeah, good to see you guys here.
Trinidad and Tobago. Always good to see
our Trinidad family here on Living Mana
Church. Just trying to see if I I know I
probably have missed some. Uh I know I
have, but um tried to catch up there.
So, you can continue to put in the chat
and we'll try to uh u say a special
welcome to you
>> as you guys are are coming in to church.
>> Amen. Amen.
>> All right. I know you're excited about
Sabbath school, but let's let's get to
the t-shirt message for today.
>> Yeah. I'm not excited about Sabbath
school.
>> You're not? Um, no. I'm actually kind of
nervous again.
>> Okay.
>> Like I was with the 10orn presentation.
So, this is going to be another one of
those
>> one of the one of another one of those
studies.
>> Okay.
>> Um, and so it needs to be shared,
>> but it's one of those buckle your seat
belts. So, just correcting you on the
excited like I can't wait to share this.
>> Well, that's okay. All right. Okay.
>> But t-shirt. Yeah, t-shirt. Want to say
all the Ohio, San Antonio, Texas. Good
to see all of you here today. And second
time from Serbia. So maybe Okay, so we
must have several people from watching
from Serbia because I've said Serbia a
few times, but welcome. Please share,
tell your friends in in your area all
about Living Mana Church. Okay. And
Ruben, I just saw your message, so I
don't know if this is your first time
attending Living Mana, but um if it is
your first time visiting with us, you
said you've always wanted to visit the
church.
>> Welcome.
>> Welcome. So happy to have you here with
us today.
>> Amen. So, okay, t-shirt. I will walk by
faith even when I cannot see.
>> Yes. Now, I'm going be honest. last
week's shirt was I could have worn it
again today, but I was like I wore it
last week, but it went
>> um it it was talking about where God
leads, he provides. Uh where he guides,
he provides. And um this kind of is just
a continuation of that. And then like on
Monday got some news that things were
might being a little bit different than
what we thought. And it was like, okay,
God, what are you doing? Where are you
go? Where are you guiding? are you
saying just stay still and and wait upon
you because maybe we just because we
don't have we're not sure about some
things. And so um this message today
just goes along with that meaning um
when you you're walking by faith. You
don't you don't know where he's leading.
Uh so sometimes the walking by faith is
just staying still.
>> Yeah.
>> Just staying still.
>> Trusting him. trusting him because you
haven't heard a direct thus sayeth the
Lord.
>> So sometimes that is difficult for us
because we don't have patience. But then
again, something I share with my clients
and always have to remind myself um you
don't want to well I don't can't say I
share it this way with my clients
because not all my clients are
Christians but but to Christians this is
you know and what I believe for myself
and other Christians is that you don't
ever want to be in a space that God has
not called you to because you will be
unhappy. You will not be happy.
>> Y that's the truth. So that's the
encouragement. Even when you don't know
what's going on or where God is leading,
if you're not sure, just stay still.
>> Just stay still.
>> Amen.
>> Because if he has the if the Holy Spirit
hasn't just moved powerfully um on your
mind to tell you like, "Yes, this is
where I'm leading you." The safest place
is to just
stay still.
>> Yeah.
>> Just wait.
>> Amen.
>> Until you know.
>> Mhm. For sure.
>> Let him cook.
>> Let him cook. We are Yeah. Let him cook.
That goes with our Sabbath school last
week. Um being spiritually God has us
spiritually blindfolded.
>> So that we can just chill and trust him
while he's cooking up the miracle.
>> That's right.
>> Yes.
>> Amen.
>> And that's for all of us.
>> All right.
>> All right. Well, we are going to go
ahead guys and jump into our um Sabbath
school for today. Again, just go ahead
and start sharing now. Let people know
uh cuz let's pray and then let's start
talking.
>> Yes.
>> You want to pray?
>> Okay.
>> Heavenly Father, thank you for this
Sabbath. Thank you for all those who are
here with us worshiping you today. Lord,
we pray for those who um are in um not
in such a great situation because of the
weather. Um and so we just pray that uh
you will work things out for them,
whatever that may be. Um Lord, and we
just ask that your Holy Spirit uh will
be here with us during this Sabbath
school in Jesus name. Amen.
>> Amen.
So I will say I will say this that I
don't think I can remember
A time when
so much is happening in the news,
in our country, around the world
>> all at once.
>> All at once that
you begin to feel overwhelmed with what
do I talk about?
>> Yeah.
>> What do I address? cuz once you address
one thing, there's 50 other things that
have just happened.
>> Mhm.
>> Within like
2 three days.
>> Mhm. And
I don't know if um
I don't know if if anyone else senses
that,
>> but
that's you know with me like looking and
watching
>> it it has become in a sense overwhelming
to just
almost like there's not enough time
to address
all the things that that need to be
addressed that should be addressed.
>> Um there's so much going on. We are
living in a different time.
>> And we kind of talked Sorry. Go ahead.
Go ahead.
>> We kind of talked about this two weeks
ago, too. There's so much going on
behind the scenes, but there's al but
there's also so much going on that's
just a distraction.
>> Mhm.
>> To what's the important things that are
really going on.
>> Yeah.
>> But it definitely feels like a different
time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So we've had three
organizations uh you know I think the
NAD Spectrum magazine
>> to do an article on an article
foundation um it was the in response to
>> the NAD did a a long uh response
>> and I think that's I didn't see the one
on spectrum but I think that's probably
the most
>> um important because the NAD is very uh
cautious like they don't just jump at
everything. Yeah. they they're not here
responding to every little thing that's
happening all of the time. So, or at
least not writing articles, publishing
articles about it. So,
>> um the fact that the church feels like
they needed to make a statement and um
about what the Heritage Foundation is uh
requesting,
I think is very um
>> significant.
>> It's very significant. And and something
they mentioned in their article that
they put that they put out um was that
it's not just that the Heritage
Foundation is requesting it, but is
requesting from um the administration
and government officials and have the
ear. They have the ear
>> of
the government.
>> Yeah.
>> This administration, I should say, to be
specific.
>> Yeah.
So there's that going on. There's, you
know, ICE is going
>> immigration. Yeah.
>> The immigration issues going on. There's
Greenland and all these different things
that are happening that again are so
overwhelming the things that are
happening in the UN. It is pretty much
um
like I said, it's like everything is
coming at you like 100 miles an hour.
Mhm.
>> Um what do you know what to grab on to
>> and what to let go?
>> Right.
>> If you've been watching us for any time,
you know that um we have consistently
said, listen, Sunday law is not going to
pass until the whirlwind happens,
>> right?
So when when you hear us today
addressing, you know, Heritage
Foundation and and some other things as
well, because we're going to be talking
about ICE, too,
>> and uh what's happening with the
immigration situation and that's
probably why you want to let people know
you need to tune in.
>> Yeah, please. And also know that you can
and when you can also ask your questions
and comments and we're Yes. Yeah, we are
>> wanting you to do that. So
there's a lot going on. But once again,
in order to understand
and not be fearful and not, you know,
the sky is falling when the sky is not
yet falling
>> that there are other things that need to
take place. We have to have a correct
understanding of prophecy.
>> So we're always going to say what?
>> Go back to back to the basics.
>> Back to the basics
>> series. You can find it on Power of the
Lamb YouTube.
>> The Matthew 24 series. Absolutely.
>> And the elephant in the room series
just
>> Yeah.
>> Binge watch.
>> Yeah. And we're going to add to that
>> the story of the 10 horns.
>> Oh, absolutely. The one we did last
week.
>> If you haven't seen it yet. Yeah. We did
it last week. Last Friday. If you have
not seen it yet, you need to go see
that. Now,
>> it was my plan to actually do a part two
and I am going to do a part two.
>> Okay. But with the things that that have
been happening over the last several
weeks, I'm actually taking a portion of
that part two that I was going to do
next Friday. It it will be next Friday.
Um,
and I'm going to be addressing some of
that today.
If the T horn study to you was was
mindblowing,
what you will see this coming Friday is,
you know, maybe the icing on the cake.
May I don't know if that's a an
appropriate term to use, but we never
really got into
we we covered the basics of here's how
it relates to what's going on today.
understanding the 10 horns, their
history, what they have done during the
dark ages and beyond, and how each one
of those horns
>> represent some form of corrupted
Christianity as it as it mends or as it
blends itself with um iron and clay,
>> right?
And we looked at the history of each one
of these horns and saw, whoa, this horn
did this during the dark ages and this
horn did and how it's all going to
culminate in that final horn
>> which we saw was the Anglo Saxon horn
>> which
um we understand to have its modern day
counterpart would have been Britain,
England and then how that translated to
the United States of America.
>> Mhm.
>> That is super significant, guys. Okay.
So, in that study, we weren't talking
about races of people because God
doesn't care
>> about races of people,
>> right? But what we saw is that to a
large degree the T horns
care about races of people
>> and lift up races of people as we saw in
the Visig Gothic horn and the Sway by
horn and the Anglo-Saxon horn and the
Alamani horn.
>> All horns
that somehow or another fused
race with Christianity.
>> Germany. Mhm.
>> Um, we saw that the Protestant refer I'm
not even going to go into we just you
just need to go back and watch. Okay.
>> Yes. And back to the basic series was
>> was just put the link was just put in
the um in the chat. So please after
late after church service today just
when in your time that is a great series
that will just
help you realize that none of these
things are happening are the final
movements um that need to happen but
they are very important and we need to
be focused.
So, so here's what I'm going to say,
guys. Like this. We need to understand
that the devil has a
a very sly way of getting us to close
our eyes to the things that are going on
around us.
>> This is very interesting.
I think for the last uh six, five, six
years um
there was this chorus
that hey we don't know where the Sunday
law is coming from. The Sunday law could
be coming from the communists. The
Sunday law could be coming from the
atheists. And how do you know it's going
to and there was really a lot of how can
you say that it's going to come from you
know the religious right? How can you
say this is being political? This is
being all these things, right?
>> I was going to say that where they where
the Sunday law is going to come from the
transgender. I'm
>> Yeah, the Sunday law is going to come
from the, you know, the
>> way they're focused on them. You think
that they were about to they were going
to do something huge, which
>> they're not. And and now you kind of
look all over Facebook and it's like
Sunday law and the Heritage Foundation
and hey guys, we got to be careful. But
wait a minute.
>> We should have known that five or six
years ago. Listen,
>> for sure.
>> Not five or six years ago. We should
have always known that,
>> right? We should have always known that
Marxism wasn't the issue, that communism
wasn't the issue, that yes, they are
issues, but it's not the prophetic
issue, right, that God's people are to
be locked on.
>> It is it is so interesting that the
Heritage Foundation
>> which was anti-COVID,
>> right? religious liberty, the same
foundation that they were on the the
whole thing of religious liberty and the
government is overstepping. And you
know, I just went back to their website
this morning just to just to make sure.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Are the very same people
>> that are now offering that are now
suggesting that we should have a Sunday
law. What about religious liberty?
>> A national day of worship.
>> A national day of worship. Where's all
the, you know, the COVID is going to
lead to this and that that and the and
the and the, you know, the Marxists are
going to this is the beginning of
religious tyranny. H
>> where is the religious tyranny
>> coming from?
There is no need for us to guess. There
is no need for us to debate because we
have always understood. Somehow or
another, many people got on this train
that is still I think
>> they cozied up
>> cozied up
>> with with
>> because oh they're they're on the right
side of things. They're godly. They are,
you know, at least they're not like the
Marxists. At least they're not like the
communists.
>> And so there was just a whole bunch of
cozying up and defending and you know,
oh this is political. this political,
you know, you shouldn't say that. And
but I think we're past that now.
Now, unfortunately,
they're still cozying up.
However,
a straight testimony
is exactly what God calls for.
Regardless of the, "Oh, you're being
political or whatever." Yeah. People
have idolized
philosophy. They've idolized nation
and as a result now
the very things that so many of us were
were on the side of and pushing now
we're like whoa whoa whoa heritage
foundation
>> it is it is it is kind of sad to see the
you know almost like the talking out of
both sides of the mouth like now we're
talking about heritage. But where was
the warning for our people? Hey, don't
go down this road.
>> Where was the warning last year and the
year before and the year before and the
year before and the year before? This is
a trap, guys. Don't fall into the
>> into the into the into the talking
points
that you're seeing in in in the media
coming from Christian nationalists. You
know, oh, Christian nationalism isn't a
thing. And again, how do you know that
it's that Sunday law is going to come
from that direction? It could come from
Yeah.
>> And it was kind of stunning to hear this
talk. Mhm.
>> But the talk is out there
>> because that kind of talk only I don't I
mean there there on a much smaller scale
may have that type of talk may have been
uh those things may have been said but
in the last 15 years or so that talk has
become louder and louder and then become
>> part of our part of our church
>> part of our church
>> part of our church. Where was that same
energy? And I always say growing up,
what we what you share here growing up
in the Seventh Day Adventist Church as a
little girl.
>> Yeah.
>> We've known this stuff.
>> Well, you didn't grow up in church, but
I always I always knew this stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, it was just like
>> ABC.
>> Yeah.
>> And so I think it's the And I'm I'm
speaking now
>> just so that we can understand, right?
We bear a responsibility in staying
silent,
>> right? You can't be silent about a
warning and then when it's in your face
be like, "Hey guys, look, Heritage Law,
I mean Heritage Foundation, Sunday law."
>> No, we have been saying and many many
among us were just like gung-ho on the
train, you know, we got to be careful of
the Marxists and all these things. So
that's not even what the Sabbath school
is about today because today we're
>> today
what I'm going to try to demonstrate as
I demonstrated with the 10 horn study.
>> Can I say this really quick though? Go
ahead.
um something that
not giving the Heritage Foundation a
compliment but because it's not but it's
a characteristic that if we would take
that on
>> we would be um
it would we would do better um for for
the gospel and for for God's cause is
that they stayed very focused
>> and quiet as they worked.
>> Yep.
Nothing was going to throw them off.
>> Of course.
>> Y
>> and when it was time to come up from
underground,
>> y
>> everything was done.
>> Y
>> project 2025 did not.
>> Oh, it's not.
>> They are
>> Yeah.
>> consistent, precise, and they
>> try to meet their target. They're not
more powerful than God,
>> but they don't get distracted.
how I feel like our people can do like
we're on this boat and then we're like,
"Oh yeah, let's come back over here."
Like just stay focused and work
>> blowing with the wind with the winds.
You know,
it it should not be a shock to us when
Turning Point USA
>> and all these other organizations that
some of us are here now cheering
>> are going to take up the same
if if they haven't done so publicly.
>> No. Turning Point and Heritage on the
same page
>> are one of the same are two sides of the
same coin.
>> Yeah.
>> Is that the way the saying goes? Yeah, I
think so.
>> Yeah, they're two sides of the same
coin. They
>> Yeah. So once again even in all this
guys
what I'm cautioning is
no Sunday law is not coming from the
Marxists. It's not coming from the from
the uh you know communists. It is also
not coming from
uh uh climate change.
>> It is also not coming from the United
Nations. I was going to say, "Yeah,
>> we're all over the place.
>> Prophecy is is is certain
>> and clear.
>> We don't need to guess. We ought not to
guess at anything." That's what the
spirit of prophecy tells us.
>> But here we are just wasting our
prophetic capital
>> by just
tossing and, you know, throwing
everything against the wall to see what
stakes.
With that said, with that said, um, what
I'm about to show you guys is kind of
like I said, what I was what I did with
the 10 horn series was basically try to
say, listen, guys, look, you got to look
at the origin.
>> If you don't understand the origin,
you're not going to understand where we
are today and why the things that are
going on today are going on. I'm going
to demonstrate that to you right now.
>> I actually have slides prepared and I
put these together this morning because
last night I wasn't planning to do this,
right? We were going to go a whole
different route and this morning I was
like, "No, we got to do this and we got
to do this this way."
>> That's how the Holy Spirit works, guys.
>> Let's
>> with him
>> because we went to sleep with something
different
>> and but that's how the Holy Spirit
works.
>> So, what I want to do, guys, what I want
to do is I'm not going to say anything
now, okay? I mean, I'm not going to make
any connections. I'm just going to do
some reading for you and some history.
And when I present Friday night, this
will be included. It's not the entire
thing. So, you're getting a sneak peek
of what I'm going to be presenting
Friday night.
>> So,
um, in 1916, there was a book written
called The Passing of the Great Race.
>> It was written by Madison Grant. And I
want to show you
I want to show you uh we're going to go
to the slides and this is just a summary
of the book. First of all, put a one in
the chat if you have heard the book
heard about the book The Passing of the
Great Race. Put a one in the chat if you
have heard about this book. And while
you're doing that, I'm going to go ahead
and go to the screen.
I'm going to look at the summary of this
book. Once again, written in 1916.
Okay, here's what it says. The book The
Passing of the Great Race by Madison
Grant presents a theory of Nordic
superiority,
claiming that the Nordic race is
inherently superior to other human
races.
Grant argues that the members of
contemporary American Protestant society
could trace their ancestry back to
colonial times and are being outbred by
immigrant and lowerass white racial
stocks.
He posits that certain parts of Europe
were underdeveloped and a source of
racial stocks
are unqualified
for the Nordic political structure of
the United States.
Grant's analysis of population studies,
economic utility factors, labor supply,
and other factors purport to show that
the consequence of this subversion was
evident in the decreasing quality of
life, lower birth rates,
and corruption of contemporary American
society. He also supports eugenics
advocating for the sterilization of
undesirabs
to solve the whole question in 100
years. Okay,
so let's pause for a second
and basically guys this book
which is a very which was a very popular
book
>> when it was published
>> basically
um
>> and did you say the year? 1916.
>> Okay.
>> 1916.
>> Um,
>> it's interesting.
>> It's interesting. Yeah.
>> I'm just thinking about Kevin Burton's
presentation
>> all around that same time.
>> I sure wish he was here right now.
>> I hope we can get him in February.
>> Maybe we'll see.
>> Pray guys that we can get Kevin Burton.
He's so soughta. But go ahead. Okay.
>> So,
uh, this book basically just the summary
of the book is that hey, listen. Um
there are inferior
races
that are infiltrating
and in essence invading America
>> to get rid of or
um bring about the book calls it racial
suicide.
So, the diminishing of the white
Anglo-Saxon race
by replacing them with lesser
uh quality races
>> from across the seas.
Okay? Now, remember, I am not making any
commentary, y'all. Mhm.
>> I'm just asking you to think
1916.
1916. Let me go ahead and let me read.
This is from page eight of the book. Uh
so that was about the book, right? That
was just a a online summary of the book.
But here's the actual book. This is page
eight, which is I believe is in is in
the introduction of the book. And here's
what it says.
History is repeating itself in America
at the present time and incidentally is
giving a convincing demonstration of the
central thought in this volume, namely
that heredity and racial predisposition
are stronger and more stable than
environment and education.
Whatever may be its intellectual
um whatever may be its intellectual, its
literary, its artistic or its musical
aptitudes as compared with other races,
the Anglo-Saxon branch of the Nordic
race is again showing itself to be that
upon which the nation must chiefly
depend for leadership,
for courage, for loyalty, for unity
and harmony of action for self-sacrifice
and devotion to an ideal.
Not that members of other races are not
doing their part. Many of them are. But
in no other human stock which has come
to this country is there displayed the
unanimity
of heart, mind, and action which is now
being displayed by the descendants of
the blue-eyed fair-haired peoples of
Northern Europe. Okay.
So,
did you all catch that?
>> What I want you to The name of the book
is entitled
um The Passing of the Great Race. Mhm.
>> And I want you to understand once again
that
the reason that I'm showing you this
is all going to tie back to Revelation
chapter 13
and verse 11
where the Bible says that there's a
nation that rises has the horns of a
lamb
>> and speaks like a dragon. Um
so
in this book the argument is that if we
don't do something
about
the people coming into our country
>> then our country is going to go down.
Mhm.
>> Our country is going to go down.
>> And our country is going to go down
because of
>> inferior stock coming into our country.
>> Now you guys please remember right
please remember
let me say this. Let me say this.
I think it is it is something telling
when
if we talk about hate,
you know, we people will not say why are
you always talking about hate?
>> If we talk about um pride, why are you
always talking about pride? If we talk
about uh anger, why you always talking
about anger? But
I think there's a there is a backlash
>> when it comes to race,
>> which is satanic,
>> racism is is a satanic thing,
>> but I think the anger of why are you
exposing this?
Well,
we're called to expose the works of
darkness.
when you see what's happening when you
read this book
>> and you understand okay wait a minute
>> so in this book wow the things I'm
hearing
>> is
that sounds a lot that I'm looking
around at what's going on today and wait
a minute so hold on I'm going to show
you something else here let's go back to
the screen and I and I want you to
understand I'm going to read another
page here listen to
The transportation lines advertised
America as a land flowing with milk and
honey. And the European government took
the opportunity to unload upon upon
careless, wealthy, and hospitable
America the sweepings of their jails and
asylums. Stop for a second. This is
1916.
And what this book is saying
is that they're sending their criminals.
>> They're sending their rapists. They're
sending the worst of their stock to
America. This is 1916.
>> Mercy.
And this book which is dedicated to
talking about the superiority
of the Protestant of Protestant America,
Anglo-Saxon America
is being threatened
because other nations are sending Let me
put it back up on the screen in case you
thought I was making this up.
The transportation lines advertised
America as a land flung with milk and
honey, and the European governments took
the opportunity to unload upon careless,
wealthy, and hospitable America the
sweepings of their jails and asylums.
The result was that the new immigration,
while it still included many strong
elements from the north of Europe,
contained a contained a large and
increasing number of the weak, the
broken,
and the mentally crippled of all races,
drawn from the lowest stratum of the
Mediterranean basin and the Balkans,
together with the hordes of the
wretched, submerged populations of the
Polish ghettos. Our jails, insane
asylums, and arms houses are filled with
this human flatsom, and the whole tone
of American life, social, moral, and
political, has been lowered and
vulgarized by them.
>> Now, you guys,
we can just stop the presentation right
here. Mhm.
>> I I don't think anything more
needs to be said.
Nothing else needs to be said.
But there's going to be more said
>> because what I want you to understand,
beloved, is that the things that we are
seeing happening now and the arguments
that we hear being made happening now
and even coming from within our own
ranks, I need you to understand where
this thing is coming from. Mhm.
>> And when we refuse to actually
acknowledge it as it is and call it out,
we're actually, it's almost as if we're
giving Satan his space and covering for
him
>> instead of being like, "Guys, here is
what's happening." And as a church, we
need to call this out together,
unitedly,
>> just like the church did
during slavery.
>> We need to have that kind of boldness.
>> Yeah.
>> And what's happening is that when we're
like, "Oh, yeah." You know, no, it's not
that. No, it's not that. No, it's not
that. Mhm.
>> But when you look at the history
>> when we understand
the history of the T horns
and what Satan will do with that final
horn
and we see what's happening now
>> you guys
how how we can say this is not important
it doesn't matter becomes a very serious
ious revelation
>> of where we are spiritually.
>> All right.
Now, I want you to see something else
and and then we're going to we're going
to we're going to show several videos in
a moment, but I want you to we're going
to read another portion from the book.
Okay. Let's go ahead and read. Efforts
to increase the birth rate of the genius
producing classes of the community while
most desirable encounter great
difficulties. In such efforts, we
encounter social conditions over which
we have as yet no control. Man has two
choices. Man has a choice of two methods
of race improvement. He can breed from
the best or he can eliminate the worst
by segregation or sterilization
in mankind. It would not be a matter of
the great difficulty of great difficulty
to secure a general consensus of public
opinion as to the least desirable. let
us say 10% of the community. When this
unemployed and unemployable human
residum has been eliminated together
with the great mass of crime, poverty,
alcoholism and feebleness associated
therewith, it would be easy to consider
the advisability of further restricting
the perpetual the perpetuation of the
then remaining least valuable types.
By this method, mankind might ultimately
become sufficiently intelligent to
choose deliberately the most vital and
intellectual strains to carry on the
race. So, let's summarize that once
again.
Here's what it's saying.
Basically,
the reason
breath.
All
right. Can you guys hear us?
>> Put a one in the chat if you could hear
us.
>> Yeah, I think they can hear us.
Okay, they're saying we're back.
All right,
>> put a one in the chat if you can see us.
>> I guess the most important thing is to
hear us.
>> All right, we're just going to talk. You
may not be able to see us.
>> Oh, they can you guys can see us. Okay.
>> Okay,
>> great. Wonderful.
>> We can't see ourselves.
>> Yeah, and that's okay. We know what we
look like.
>> All right,
>> we can see we can see your uh we can see
the chat. We can see your comments. So,
okay. That's a blessing. Maybe we should
just say a prayer over the technology.
It could be to be honest with you. Um,
what time is it? I think our storm just
started here and I told our
producer that we wouldn't be affected
but by God's grace we won't. So, okay.
Yeah,
>> let's pray. All right. I think we should
pray over I think we should pray moving
forward.
>> Yeah. Heavenly Father, just uh be with
this equipment, Lord. Let this storm not
remove or not not disrupt what we need
to say, Lord.
>> Amen.
>> What you need to say to your people,
Lord. So please speak and please Lord um
be with the equipment. We pray in Jesus
name. Amen.
>> Amen.
>> All right. So
>> Okay, they can see us. That's great. All
right. Perfect.
>> The goal, one of the goals is to have
more kids. Now, if you have been hearing
this um this talk
>> Mhm.
>> coming from uh those in Christian
nationalism
>> about having more kids, we need to have
more kids. Put a one in the chat if
you've heard that talk. And you may have
just been like, "Oh, you know, um yeah,
we uh we we we've heard that, but you
know, it's it's not a big deal.
>> It's not a big deal. Maybe they're just
saying it for whatever reason.
>> I need you to understand
where that's coming from. M
>> and I'm going to show you that it is in
fact coming from the idea of of
outbreeding
the the population that is bringing evil
to America.
That's what's that that's what they're
after.
>> Listen,
>> so this book was written in 1916.
>> Okay.
>> In 1924, I'm going to go back to the
screen here. Let's see if we can get
this slide up on the screen.
The 1924 Johnson Reed Act, also known as
the National Origins Act, was a pivotal
pivotal piece of legislation that
significantly impacted the immigration
landscape of the United States. It set
quotas for immigration based on national
origins, favoring northern and western
Europeans, European groups, while
largely excluding those from southern
and eastern Europe.
This act was rooted in fears of economic
competition,
urban overcrowding
and racial purity notions propagated by
eugenics.
The axe provision led to a dramatic
decline in immigration particularly from
Europe until changes were eventually
made in 1965.
The legacy of the 1924 act is
intertwined with broader themes of race,
ethnicity, and national identity in
American history, often sparking debates
about immigration that resonate to this
day. So, what I want you to understand
is that partially as a result of that
book, The Passing of the Great Race, you
have the 1924 Johnson Reed Act
addressing immigration and saying no
more undesirabs coming in.
This is the origin of our immigration
laws in this nation.
>> Okay,
that was 1924. I'm going to go back to
the screen and now we're going to go to
1929.
>> The Undesirable Aliens Act of 1929, also
known as BLE Law, and we're going to
talk about who BLE is just in a moment
here, was a significant piece of
legislation that aimed to restrict
Mexican immigrants to the United States.
It made unlawful entry entering entering
the country a misdemeanor and returning
after a felony a felony with se with
severe penalties. The law criminalized
border crossings outside of official
port of entries marking a shift in US
immigration policy during the 1920s. Ble
a segregationist
and anti-immigrant.
So the guy who pushed for this policy
was a racist.
>> Let's go back to the screen. Ble is a
segregationist and anti-immigration was
a key figure in the legislative push to
limit Mexican immigration which was a
major concern during that period. The
law's enforcement was closely tied to
the Great Depression, leading to federal
government coercion of Mexicans in the
US into repatri repatriation by
threatening penalties
and conducting immigration raids
targeting those who would not prove
their legal legal status. You guys, by
the end of the 1930s, over 44,000 cases
of unlawful entry against Mexicans were
prosecuted by US attorneys.
Okay, we can come back,
>> you guys. Um Oh, I'm sorry.
No, no, no. That's fine. That's fine. We
we can we can leave this out. So
you guys what I need you to understand
a and the more that that you study this
concept of the ten horns
>> you guys the more you are going to
realize
that one of the driving factors behind
mystery Babylon
>> apostate Protestantism
one of the reasons that it is called
apostate is not just because of its
false doctrine,
but its false spirit,
>> its spirit of pride,
>> and it's not saying that that is limited
to one group of people,
but a large moving factor that you're
going to see
is Christian nationalism,
which is by and charge
tied to the very same concept that led
the Jews in Jesus's day to reject Jesus.
>> National pride and those Gentiles aren't
like us. We are God's chosen
>> people. And as a result, we are by
nature better than the Samaritans. Mhm.
>> We are by nature better than the gentile
gentiles. There's nothing new under the
sun.
But what we're see and what we're seeing
here, beloved, is that the same spirit
that led to the rejection of Christ,
which was which was religious
nationalism based on race,
>> will be included
>> in the reason for, check this out y'all,
a national Sunday law.
Now, I'm going to leave that alone until
Friday night
because you may have never heard that
before.
>> But there's a reason Revelation 13:11
describes this beast as having horns of
a lamb and speaking like a dragon.
There's a reason why our pioneers looked
at that verse and said one of the key
identifying factors of this beast is the
fact of is is the fact that
>> of its racism.
Not everybody,
but the philosophy of racism tied in
with Christianity and and we have by and
large said, "Yeah, well that was in the
1800s. That's not going to have anything
to do with the Sunday law." But I'm
telling you
>> that as we study this out further, we
are going to see that national pride
and the Sunday law
will be
connected.
Cerebral Brienne, just thank you for
that, man.
Thank you for that. I I see your message
and and I thank you for that. Praise
God.
Praise God. And would to God that
we were saying this more.
>> That other people who may have never
heard this before
would be like, "Oh, I get this now. I'm
understanding this."
>> So, let me get back to my point, which
is and then and then we're going to look
at several videos and then we're going
to wrap this up.
the National Sunday law will be a sign.
And yes, Ellen White definitely said
that racism would play a role in the
last days, that slavery would be
revived.
The national Sunday law I believe will
be one of the signs will be a symbol of
American greatness.
>> It will become a symbol not of
worshiping Jesus. That will be the
pretext.
But in reality, it will be that this is
what sets aside American exceptionalism,
American greatness, American
nationalism.
>> The two are going to tie in together.
>> It is inevitable.
The Bible doesn't just speak of
Revelation 13:11 and say, "Here's why
this nation begins like this, but then
it gets better or then this goes away."
As we look at the history of this nation
and again you guys the history of the
nation does not mean that that the
entire nation is corrupt. There are good
people in this. Praise God right
>> for the people the white people that
fought in the civil war
>> to abolish slavery.
>> Praise God for the people who have
always stood for the right
regardless of color regard Praise God
for those people. We're not saying that,
oh this is all America. No. But there is
an element within America that is using
Christianity
as a chosen horse
to re to in an effort.
>> The Christianity is a front.
>> It's a front
>> because behind the scenes
it is corruption
>> for power.
It is corruption for power for power of
a certain, you know, segment of people
and nobody else. And as long as you
grant that we are the supreme, then
you're we're good with you.
>> And not to keep plugging the T horns
presentation from two weeks ago, but
you'll see that that spirit was
throughout history.
>> Yep.
>> With all the T horns.
>> So this is no different. So
>> Christianity is just it's a tool to
>> to for the corruption.
>> Absolutely.
>> Behind the scenes.
>> This same book, The Passing of the Great
Race,
>> is one of the original books that talked
about the great replacement theory. And
it doesn't call it a theory. It just
says, listen, uh um
immigrants are replacing the Caucasian
race.
And if we don't do something about it,
the greatest race on earth which
represents western values and and hard
work and the finer uh and higher no
values of life and and and nobleness of
character which is all in the bloodline.
>> It's all in the bloodline. Their thought
process is that it is genetic. It is
passed down. It is bloodline. That was a
whole thing about the Anglosaxon
or the Nordic race. So their whole thing
is
they are try they are we are going to be
replaced and if we don't do something
and this is why the immigration's law
the immigration law of 1924 and then
1929 both passed
>> for fear of replacement.
>> Replacement.
All right,
>> let's go to the screen, you guys. And
now we're going to pull this together.
Don't be mad. Just Just listen to the
truth, you guys. Let's make it make
sense now.
>> Let's make it make sense now. All right,
let's go back to the screen, and I want
you to watch.
We're just going to outreed these
people. We are. I mean, we're just going
to out We're going to have more babies
and 20 years from now, they're going to
say, "Why is the country so right-wing?
Well, you were too busy having abortions
and having gay sex and we got married
and had kids and we will repopulate the
species.
>> By the way,
>> I'm not kidding. By the way,
>> by the way, you can be left, right,
center, logical, emotional. That is by
far the most logical argument you just
gave statistically that cannot be argued
because it's proven. It's going to take
two years.
>> Give us some time, everybody. Buy us
some time. Buy the Constitution some
time.
>> The key though, we got to have more of a
level of kids.
>> Well, yes. We got to get our
testosterone rates high. young ladies
got to get married and we have to have
the babies. And by the way, I mean the
the the the Bet David family, you guys
are doing your part. Having children is
not a leftwing value. The truth of the
matter is this is that if leftwing
people keep on not having kids, whether
it be by abortion or, you know, being in
homosexual relationships, how exactly
they think this thing is going to work.
All right. Did y'all see that whole
thing or do I need to play it again?
>> They I think they did. They're delayed,
so they saw it.
>> All right. So, I was just seeing some of
you were saying that you weren't hearing
any volume on the video. So, I just want
to make sure
>> before it started.
>> Okay.
>> Because we're delayed.
>> Yeah. All right. So, we're talking about
outreeding them. Outbreeding who?
Outbreeding who? Outbreeding
the people that are No. No. You know,
it's just the left is mentioned,
>> but what is what are they talking about?
the people that are coming here and
overtaking the country.
Let me just show you just so you think
this is not a one-off. We're going to go
to another video. Let's go. Ready?
Southern border is of course the great
replacement. They're trying to replace
us demographically. They're trying to
make the country less white. They're
trying to make the country more like the
third world. The dumping ground of the
planet is the United States southern
border. And the secret is out. The
rapists, the thugs, the murderers,
fighting age males, they're coming from
across the world, from China, from
Russia, from Middle Eastern countries,
and they're coming in and they're coming
in and they're coming in and they're
coming in
and Speaker Johnson does nothing. It is
an anti-white agenda.
And there's another story where the only
reasonable explanation you would do
something like this is because you hate
white people. And some people say, "Oh,
Charlie, come on. There's other reasons
why they want the border policy." No,
no, no. If you read their literature,
you spend time around them, the
contempt, the resentment that the
left-wing ruling class has for white
Anglo-Saxon Protestant males
is real. Even beyond that, they can't
win the white vote. No matter how hard
they try, you look at the white vote,
they can't win it. They lost it by 20
and 17% in the last two presidential
races. They can't win it. And so, how do
you win over white voters? You don't.
You just bring in more third worlders
and you dilute, aka replace them.
Please understand what I mean when I say
the reason it is important to understand
origins is because when you're listening
to something like this and you're just
like oh you know I mean maybe that's
just you know this individual's personal
thought.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Or I heard it
someplace else too. Someone else say but
maybe it's true. You guys, when you go
back and understand, wait a minute,
>> this was this a book was written in 1916
called the passing of the great race,
which talks about third world countries
and replacing white people. And that is
the plot of the enemy. And if we don't
do something, if we don't have more
babies,
>> you guys,
>> and I don't I don't know if our viewing
audience follows uh Turning Point USA or
Heritage Foundation close enough to know
that they are saying the exact same
thing about having specifically right
now they're saying have more babies.
even to women, don't seek out your
career right now. Have babies first. Do
the career later just because we don't
want the the numbers to go down.
>> It it's called
>> And when I first heard that, I was like,
why are you why?
>> But this
>> or just about family.
>> You could have family at any time or
point in time in your life. It doesn't
have to be
>> in your early 20s.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's keep going. Here's another one.
What appears to them is we're replacing
nationalborn American, nativeborn
Americans to permanently transform the
political landscape.
>> Is it really they want to remake the
demographics of America to ensure
they're that they stay in power forever?
>> They can't win re-election in 2022
unless they bring in a large number of
new voters to replace the voters that
are already here. That's what this is
about. We have an invasion in this
country.
>> Invasion.
>> An invasion. We're going to keep going.
Let's press first press play on this
next one. Almost there, guys. Almost
done.
Democrats who want to replace you. the
American voters with newly amnestied
citizens.
>> Congress is not going to act because one
party has a vested interest in changing
the population. If you use the term is
an invasion that's not anti-Hispanic,
it's a fact. I have less political power
because they're importing a brand new
electorate. Why should I sit back and
take that?
I think this will be the last election
that the Republicans have a chance of
winning because you're going to have
people flowing across the borders.
You're going to have illegal immigrants
coming in and they're going to be
legalized and they're going to be able
to vote. And once that all happens, you
can forget
on immigration. You better get your act
together or you're not going to have
Europe anymore. You got to get your act
together. And we, you know, as you know,
last month we had nobody entering our
country. Nobody. Shut it down. And we
took out a lot of bad people that got
there with Biden. Biden was a total
stiff and what he allowed to happen. But
you're allowing it to happen to your
countries. And you got to stop the this
horrible invasion that's happening to
Europe. Many countries in Europe. Some
people, some uh leaders have not let it
happen
and they're not getting the proper
credit. They they should I could name
them to you right now, but I'm not going
to embarrass the other ones. But stop
this immigration is killing Europe.
So you guys
when we understand
as I said go back and pick up that book
if you will.
>> What I want you to understand is th this
is not innocent talk.
>> This is not just you know um
oh this is just security. It's you guys
it's security of a particular ideal.
It's security of a particular thought
pattern.
>> And the more we put our heads in the
sand and say, "Uh, pastor, I don't want
to hear about this." And, you know, uh,
why don't we talk about other things and
this is, you know, the race card. No,
this is not the race card. The race card
is a re racism is a real thing.
I want to say like when we when we say
those things, organizations like the
Heritage Foundation and Turning Point
USA are like, "Yeah, don't talk about
it." But we're still working.
>> We're still
>> And we're still doing things behind the
scenes.
>> We're still working.
>> So, we could bury our heads in the sand
and not have a um just
a study and a conversation about what's
really going on. Um or we can uh just
act like it's not happening, but it's
happening. Yeah. Um
what we see happening today with ICE,
>> what we see happening today
in our nation,
>> I I am telling you with the Heritage
Foundation
with
if we if we don't step back from the Oh
yeah, the Democrats
or oh yeah the if we don't step back
from that kind of thinking
>> and step back and say wait a minute guys
this is king of the north king of the
south
>> Daniel 11 that we've been told about
that we have
>> studied that we understand
>> if we don't step back and and and expose
the enemy in all that he does
>> because right now I think what's
happening is that there's A lot of
people covering for this.
They're covering for the open and
blatant racism happening under the
disguise of Christianity
>> and even beginning to mimic these
things. Let me tell you
>> when
>> again go back and see the ten horns.
>> Somebody might hear that type of
statement and be like, "What do you mean
Christianity is like being used in that
way?" But that study was so eye
openening. Yeah.
>> From the history of it all.
>> Listen y'all, let me give you one more
seed from this book which totally
shocked me.
>> In this book, the you remember earlier
when I read about Anglo Anglo-Saxon
Protestants. Mhm.
>> The book literally argues
that the reason that they should reject
Christian uh Catholicism
was because the Catholic Church didn't
care what race you were if you
converted, which means they were just
about power. So if you were if you were
Mexican and you converted, if you were
Indian, you converted, they'd be like,
"Cool, we have more people in our ranks
to make the Catholic Church more
powerful." But as Anglo-Saxon Americans,
uh, Protestant, we need to understand
that we must reject this from
Catholicism and we must protect our
Anglo-Saxon Protestant heritage. That's
literally what the book argued
>> in 1916. in 1916.
>> If you go back and look at that study on
the on the 10 horns, you will see
that part of the
I believe that what corrupted the
Protestant Reformation is when they
began to tie in the Anglo-Saxon
uh uh theology
>> that hey, we're not like those
Catholics. We got Anglo-Saxon blood in
us and and and we are a different breed
and that was part of the reformation
which many people do not know and
understand. It makes sense why
>> it makes sense why Revelation 13:11 is
described as a beast with horns of a
lamb that speaks as a dragon. It is
Protestant and yet has dragonlike
attributes to it.
>> It's interesting this that you're
bringing out right now. I obviously
hadn't read the book, just really heard
of the book uh in the last 48 hours,
maybe 24 hours.
>> Um 12 hours.
>> Yeah, maybe that. But it makes sense
because when you think of Catholicism
with all of its issues, so don't take
this the wrong way. it it definitely
plays a role
>> in the in everything. But
when it comes to racism,
because it's a worldwide church and
there's what what probably well one
billion yeah
>> Catholics around the world and it's you
know it it's
doesn't um
>> you don't I'm not saying there's no
racism with Catholicism.
>> Catholicism is global. Protestantism is
American,
>> right? And so
because their reach is so far and just
so it's so diverse,
>> you just you don't hear that. And don't
get me wrong, it's it has other
problems. It has other issues,
>> of course.
>> But
>> it's the first beast,
>> right?
>> So,
>> but I find it interesting that the
Protestants had to reject that aspect of
Catholicism.
um of being so far reaching and so
welcoming to everyone.
>> They had to reject that. That's
>> and and Protestantism is saying we need
to reject Catholicism because of that.
>> At least that's what this book is
arguing.
>> Not because of the change of the Sabbath
or not because of the wrong
understanding. Not
>> not because of what Yeah. Right.
>> which is stunning.
>> Which is very stunning.
>> Stunning. So you guys, th this is this
is the thing I want you to understand as
we're looking around at what's going on
today. Don't don't excuse it as,
you know, well, what about immigration?
Okay, immigration. Yeah. I mean, nobody
wants criminals coming in their country,
but criminals can come from anywhere.
>> Criminals live in our country. Mhm.
>> Criminality is not an immigration
problem, you guys.
>> It's not. Criminality is a human
problem. And until we
we stop treating criminality as a
outside of America problem.
>> It's a problem with other nations and
other races. Mhm.
>> Then we have serious issues
>> because we're actually falling into that
ideology
>> that somehow or another
we don't have those issues here in
America because we're American.
>> If no more immigrants came into this
country ever,
crime would still be a problem in
America. Mhm.
>> Because there there is a thing called
the human heart that still lives in
every human being that is still present
in every human being in America.
>> Crime is a heart issue, not an
immigration issue.
>> That is the bottom line.
>> Most definitely. And um since we're
doing
um I don't want to say world news in the
Bible, but because we're talking about
events um that are happening right now,
um
you know, I can say that
even dealing with um
the immigration issue that people have
wanted to deal with in America. um what
ICE is doing on so many levels is not
what um the news may make you think like
so many Americans are just like that's
what they wanted is what ICE was doing
what ICE is currently doing especially
um well what they're doing all over but
in Minnesota right now is the highlight
but
>> um that is not what the majority of
Americans wanted to be done
>> and to handle that situation
>> a and even if it was Like my thing is
I'm not here.
>> There's American citizens dying.
>> That's right.
And and regardless of all this guys,
what I want you to understand is that
when we remain silent
>> on issues like this,
when we excuse in our minds issues like
this,
>> when we become the ones on the chopping
block, there will be no one to stand for
us.
>> Mercy. And how will you ex will you
excuse it then when it comes to you?
>> We it is a deriviction of duty and I've
been saying this for the last seven
years now
>> that so many of us have gone on this
train of
>> all these conspiracies
>> with no evidence for any such con. We do
other that are not in line with Bible
prophecy,
>> but the things that are clearly in line
with Bible prophecy that we can
demonstrate from history. We can say,
"Hey guys, listen. You want to know
where this anti-immigrant stuff is is
coming from? Let me take you back to the
origin.
>> Let me show you that the people who
originated these laws were
segregationists and racist.
Let me show you that all this talk
about, you know, we need to have more
babies and they're trying to replace
white America, Anglo-Saxon, Protestant
America, literally,
>> you know, oh, that's this book.
>> And I think the organizations that are
saying that,
>> um, Heritage Foundation, Turning Point
USA, they would say we we were we're
talking to all Americans and so America
is diverse, so everybody have babies.
But that's not the audience that they're
talking to because they're following
>> y
>> is not the diverse part.
>> It's a very very very small minority. Um
the diverse part of America is doesn't
follow Heritage Foundation or Turning
Point USA. Very small minority does.
>> So they're not talking to the masses of
America.
>> Yep. I I did a message
many years ago,
>> eight years ago, uh the hidden agenda
behind racism.
And in that message, I was sharing how
>> six years ago,
>> six years,
>> in that message, I was sharing how Satan
was the original racist,
>> right? And his racism was against the
human race,
>> and what he implemented in the human
race was how can I get the human race to
hate one another? and think that one
race is better than the other.
>> And you saw that demonstrated
in the Jews in Jesus' day.
>> You saw it demonstrated. He was able to
have Jesus, God's own people, reject the
Messiah because they he didn't come the
way that he thought they he wasn't
he wasn't
the Messiah that they wanted him to be.
And if that was what was what led to the
to the rejection of Christ in those days
and we now see that there is this plague
of continued racism
in our country.
Thank you for putting it in this stream.
The hidden agenda behind racism. And we
now see that there we see that from the
inception of this country there have
been good Americans and there have been
bad Americans. And the bad Americans
happen to be at least in a lot of cases
happens to be those that are hiding
behind Christianity. Hey, slavery is
good. Why? Because Christianity because
because Jesus, you know, said uh Paul
wrote uh slaves obey your masters.
When we fail to understand, I'm g come
back to this you guys.
When we fail to understand that sin is a
heart problem and not an immigration
problem,
that sin is a human problem and not an
immigration problem. See, the devil
always codes
evil with good.
>> That's what he does.
>> It's not just evil. It's good and evil.
>> And so,
uh, protecting American ideals. And that
sounds like, yeah, because we want, you
know, purity and righteousness and
holiness, holiness and
>> to restore the family.
>> Restore the family. But the way that you
do that is not through immigration laws.
The way that you do that is through
preaching the gospel.
>> That's what you do as a Christian
entity.
>> The government can't restore the family.
>> Ask the government
to enforce your religious beliefs
>> because in doing so, you are creating an
iron and clay system.
>> Right?
Jesus did never said depend upon the
government to ensure your Christian
beliefs.
>> So
>> to ensure a Christian society,
>> right? I heard.
>> And as Go ahead, go ahead.
>> As long as we fall for the narrative
of the beast
that there are certain people who are
better than others because they're not
from this country.
You guys, that is a spirit. That is the
spirit
of pride. It's a spirit of the devil.
It's a spirit of of of enmity against
God. It is everything that God stands
against.
>> And this is why God so often put laws
about the immigrant in the Bible.
>> None of which you see
>> make sure the immigrants don't come into
your country.
Mhm.
>> You never see God
>> making a law about protecting
the the the
uh the population
>> of Israel.
>> If an immigrant comes into your space,
>> treat him like a brother.
>> Right?
>> That's the spirit of Christianity.
You don't keep you don't keep crime out
by keeping immigrants out.
>> You keep crime out by preaching the
gospel.
>> And that's not what's happening,
>> right?
>> So we want laws to protect and
understand it is these same it is the
same philosophy. Laws will keep the the
the the unlawful out.
>> Laws will keep the wicked out. that is
going to lead to the law
>> which will represent you keep this then
you're on good grounds you're one of us
you're down with us and that's a Sunday
law
>> right
>> that the philosophy that laws
government laws
will ensure righteousness is exactly
what will lead to a national Sunday law
>> ensuring righteousness
>> it's the true foundation it's the true
meaning of legalism
It is legalism to the core.
>> To the core.
>> We're going to use the government
>> to ensure that our Christian values are
not overrun. But but in this case,
>> the spirit of the 10 horns.
>> That's right. It's a spirit of the 10
horns. And in this case, it's not the
Christian value.
>> It's the bloodline value.
>> Right.
>> That's what it really is. It's the
bloodline value. Again,
>> praise God that we have so many people
in the Adventist church who are not of
that mentality.
>> Amen.
>> Right?
>> Who are like, "No, it when you're
>> it's the blood of Jesus that counts.
>> Not not this blood or that blood or
white blood or black or black blood.
It's the blood of Jesus that counts."
>> However, that is not the case with
everybody.
>> Because all people aren't converted.
And so there is
a a a
spirit of pride
that if it doesn't come out outright and
say it because it's not cool to do that
now,
>> right?
>> But you say it in different ways,
>> They're trying to replace us,
>> right?
>> They're trying to replace us.
>> There there there is so much there is
>> there's so much to say. And I just
wanted to say that, you know, some of
the things that we just kind of said and
didn't spend a lot of time on like, oh,
like um, you know, strengthen the the
the
family um, and family values and all of
these things coming back. Those are all
wonderful things. f you know two two
parent home fathers and mothers together
raising their children and you know not
you know if
>> all of these things are very good things
but the red flags is when you're wanting
when like if just like Heritage
Foundation and Turning Point USA they
are very open that they are basically
lobbyist if you will yeah
>> and I don't think they're organized
registered lobbyists but they're
lobbyists to lobby the administration or
the or the government to make that
happen.
>> Those are uh whether that's a day of of
of worship, a national day of worship,
um you know, trying to like we're going
to pass laws that are going to, you
know, make the family um a stronger,
better place. As a marriage and family
therapist, I know that that's not that's
not what it it takes. If that's what it
took, I would be out of a job, right?
It's like, okay, government passed laws
and it's going to make all the fathers
stay at home with their kids and be
happily married to the to their to their
wives and and raise great children
because the government passed a law.
Absolutely not.
>> Absolutely not. That's not what it's
going to take to make supposedly society
better. So, I'm just saying that some of
these things that Turning Point USA or
even um the Heritage Foundation might
say that sounds good or even like, oh,
that's the Christian value. The the
negative and the and the part that we
have to um be looking at is they want
the government to enforce it.
And basically, and Christians like to,
some Christians like to hear that type
of stuff because it almost just makes us
be able to be lazy Christians.
>> Yeah.
>> Because, oh, well, the government's just
going to make people do it. Not change
their heart,
>> but just be a legalistic front
Christianity,
>> which is what the papacy was,
>> which is the T horns. It's the spirit of
the T horns.
>> And again, I I'm going to say this in
closing.
It's not everywhere. So, I want y'all to
think about this, right? It's not
everywhere
>> that uh people are not allowed to come
into America.
>> So for example, Southern Africa, South
Africa,
>> right? There's been a whole like, hey,
you're from South Africa, come we'll
take you.
>> The white farmers in South Africa
because they're being persecuted. Look
at where look at where
>> there's other European nations, too. Um
Yeah. Yeah. There wasn't South Africa.
Look at the nations that are being no
you can't come or you're going to bring
crime and then and it falls right in
line what the book said certain European
nations other European nations northern
European but other European no no we're
not going to go with you guys and this
is the thing you guys once again once
again
>> when we continue to close our eyes
>> to the to the satanic movements of the
enemy what's going to happen is we
become blind to it.
>> And when you become blind to it, you
excuse it. And when you excuse it, you
are brought into the same spirit. You
are now merging with the same spirit of
deception.
>> So that by the time this crisis hits,
this whirlwind hits, this overwhelming
uh uh uh storm that Ellen White said is
coming, when that hits, you have
compromised so much. little by little,
step by step,
>> that when the crisis hits, you see
things in the very same way as the
opposition. And this is exactly what
Ellen White was talking about. We have
so come to view things in the same light
as the opposition. And when she says the
opposition,
please understand, she's not talking
about Marxism as the opposition. She's
not talking about communism as the
opposition. She's talking about
Protestantism.
>> She's not talking about the UN.
How is it possible that we will begin to
see things so much so I've now even
heard this? They're trying to replace
white people within our church.
>> People within our church now freely
saying, "Yeah, this is this is an attack
on white people."
white people are they're trying to
replace white people and get rid of
white people and it's like wait a minute
how is this a part of the great
controversy
>> what
>> the devil's plan is listen yes the
devil's plan is to get rid of white
people and black people and Mexican
people and every other race of people
that has always been his plan
>> right
>> but his plan is to make us think that
somebody else
is trying to do it
>> or to actually get someone else to try
to do it.
>> All right,
we're going to wrap this up.
>> So, part two of the Ten Horns is part
this Friday
>> of the T horns this Friday night. Um,
don't miss it, you guys. What I shared
here this morning is only a portion. And
you know what? In case you're like,
"Pastor, did you make this?" go back and
get the book and read it for yourself.
It is so important that we research for
ourselves because unless we do so, we
don't know the context of these
statements that are being made. We're
just thinking, oh, you know, they just
said this and oh, they're talking about
having more babies and you know, okay,
that's a cool thing
>> until you see, oh,
this is where this comes from.
>> And then it all begins to make sense.
You guys,
>> don't be deceived. Put down
the Babylon juice,
>> the wine,
and please let me stop banging the
table, Jason. And please, please, please
>> study like you have never studied before
>> because when you begin to come down on
the wrong side of this thing,
I'm telling you, it will not end well.
>> It will not end well.
All right.
>> Amen. Amen. We want you to continue to
worship with us. This is church, guys.
This is not even the divine worship.
This was Sabbath school. Uh we are
thankful for all of you um just staying
with us uh throughout this first uh
segment, but we are going to enter into
the divine worship here um in just a
moment. We're going to pray. Do you want
to just talk about what your sermon is?
>> So um my sermon today is entitled a
prepared place. It is based off of John
14 1-3. I go to prepare a place for you.
And if I go um to prepare a place, I
will come again and receive you unto
myself, that where I am, there you may
be also. Um but
it is not
what
>> you think.
>> You think
>> it never is.
>> So please
make sure to join us and um you'll be
blessed.
>> Yes. Please continue to worship with us
um as we go into the divine worship
service. You will uh be blessed. You can
put your prayer request in the chat. We
have our prayer team that's going to be
coming on shortly that will be praying
over your prayer request. And so you
don't want to miss the worship
experience that's uh going to happen
during the divine worship service. So
continue to worship with us. We're going
to end in prayer and we will see you in
church.
>> Let's pray. Heavenly Father, thank you
Lord for speaking to us today.
>> Lord, uh we pray that we will not um
that we will have eyes salv Lord that we
may see and rightly discern the things
that are going on before us. Lord, Lord,
we know that this nation is headed for a
place that is not good. Lord, help us
Lord to understand how we can stand in
this time and not be caught up and and
and
ultimately deceived by what is coming.
Lord, it is deception in the little
things that will ultimately lead to the
deception in the biggest thing. So Lord,
please help us to be on the right side
of these issues, Lord, which is your
side. Help us, Lord, to do and to
believe what you believe about all that
is going on now. Help us, Lord, to
follow the prophetic word that has been
given to us, Lord. And we thank you,
Lord. We thank you Lord for opening our
eyes and for and for continuing to show
us your truth. In Jesus name we pray. Be
with us as we enter into the divine
service. In Jesus name we pray. Amen.
>> Amen. Amen. Continue to worship with us.
In the jungles of the Yucatan Peninsula,
there's a dark underworld hidden from
sight. A place of intrigue, fascination,
and mystery.
It is below the surface, hidden beneath
the veil of the limestone ground we walk
upon. In order to see it, you must be
willing to move out of your comfort
zone. You must venture beyond your fears
and boldly confront the uncertainties of
the unknown. You must penetrate into
rocky portals and plunge into the liquid
darkness.
But it's in this deep mysterious
darkness that the light is more
distinctly seen.
The cenotes of Kintanaro are the
thresholds of the largest underground
river in the world. The Riviera Raaya is
a 430 mi network of caverns and caves
flooded with the only potable water in
the region. This vast underground
labyrinth is a life source of the flat,
humid jungle peninsula. As rain falls,
it's filtered through the soft, porous
limestone, adding to the immensity
beneath the rock. When the rocks become
weak, it falls under its own weight,
creating these massive sink holes. A
cenote is a wound in the earth that
exposes the veins of life-giving water
below. Considered by the ancient Mayas
as the sacred portals of the underworld
where their deities resided. Fresh
openings for explorers to see the
glories of the underworld.
Most will never see it for themselves,
but the explorer in me itches for
adventure and thirst for discovery. It
is a place that is relatively easy to
get to, but very hard to leave. As the
light of the noonday sun pierces through
the holes in the limestone rock, it
creates spotlights of illumination
penetrating the darkness below. The
otherworldly scenery of the topography
mixed with the weightlessness in the
water combined with the silence and
sound of bubbles and the stark contrast
of light and darkness is nothing short
but epic.
Being deep down here where most have
never been makes me feel like I'm in
another world. It's like I've entered
into another reality and passed into a
completely different dimension. A deeper
dimension where the noise is silence,
life slows down, where the stress of the
surface is transformed into peace like a
river.
Words are inadequate to describe the
surrealism of this sacred underground
world. You must come and see and
experience it for yourself. But just as
beautiful as the scenery of the ancient
cenotes are the sublime lessons it
teaches to those whose minds take the
time to sink below the surface of a mere
outward adventure. As I've mused upon
the message of the cenotes, here are
some of the lessons it has taught me. A
cenote is a sinkhole, a weak spot in the
rock that has lost its strength to hold
anything up. When the pressure from
above and the support from below
diminishes, the structure becomes weak
and it collapses into the abyss below.
So a cenote is literally a fracture that
leads to a fall. A fault that leads to a
failure. A weakness that is broken under
pressure and has lost all strength to
hold itself up.
My friends, life is kind of like this.
There are so many pressures that people
face living in this broken world.
Perhaps you yourself have felt crushed
under the unbearable weight of this
world of sin. Maybe every earthly
support you trusted in has failed. And
as a result, you've fallen into a
sinkhole of discouragement and despair.
Maybe people have disappointed you,
political parties have frustrated you,
friends have betrayed you, family have
forsaken you, or society has discarded
you, and due to the paralyzing
pressures, your physical body and your
mental health has reached the breaking
point. Or maybe the failures of your own
foolish mistakes have caused you to fall
and you've lost all strength to hold
yourself up. Well, if this is you,
please allow me to remind you that just
like the cenotes of the Yucatan
Peninsula, your disappointment and fall
doesn't have to be your end. It can be
the beginning of a deeper illumination,
an opportunity for the darkness within
to be dispelled by the light from above,
a spiritual opening to something better
than the stuff on the surface. a crack
in our character that needs to be broken
so that we can be transformed with a
completely new purpose. A space where
the empty caverns of our lives can be
filled with new desires and new meaning.
My friends, I want you to know that the
great God of heaven wants to penetrate
the deepest, darkest areas of your life.
He wants to remove the covering you hide
behind and pierce the hard outward
exterior with the light of his amazing
love and the warmth of his blessed hope.
And when we allow the divine light to
shine in us, our brokenness and failures
then becomes redeemed for a deeper
purpose. Our lives become a new opening,
a fresh well from which flows a deeper
and clearer revelation, an illuminating
exposure to the surface world of the
depth of God's beautiful grace and
redeeming power. So don't lose hope in
the sinkhole. All is not lost if you've
fallen into the abyss. There is beauty
in the unseen realm and sweet serenity
in the cenotes of life. For God's light
shines even in the darkest, deepest and
most discouraging moments. So look to
him in the darkness. Seek him in the
cenotees and he will guide you to the
light.
We hope you've been blessed and inspired
by this new Reflections of Hope episode.
This episode is one of many that's been
produced all over the world. If you
haven't done so yet, please give our
video a like, share it with your
friends, and please follow us on
Instagram, Facebook, and YouTube. If
you'd like to see more inspiring
episodes and get access to much more
uplifting content, please go now to
patreon.com/revelationof
hope and sign up to be a member of our
Patreon page. Your monthly support will
not only give you early access to many
more inspiring videos, but it will also
enable us to continue to produce more of
these cinematic object lessons from
nature. Our goal is to produce and
release these episodes much more
frequently. So, please prayerfully
consider partnering with us so that we
may continue to share the hope of Jesus
all over the world. Thank you so much
for your support. Aloha and Marinata.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Heat up
here.
Welcome back, Living Mana Church family.
It's so good to have you here with us,
still worshiping with us. Please put in
the chat where you are viewing from so
we can say a special welcome to you. If
this is your very first time worshiping
with Living Mana Church, please put a
one in the chat. We want to tell you a
little bit more about our church. And
we're so happy to have some of you guys
are here because of the winter storm
that is uh hitting a a big part of
America. And so maybe you couldn't
actually make it to your physical church
today, but we welcome you and are happy
that you are worshiping with us today.
Please put a one in the chat. This is
your first time. Let us know if you did
not put during Sabbath school time where
you were viewing from. Uh please let us
know now because again we want to say a
special welcome to you. You know the
first uh segment, the first program, it
was such a blessing. It was a lastm
minute change in what we were going to
talk about and I um am just excited for
this study just for what it is showing
us from the Bible, from prophecy and
tying into current events, why things
are happening and going on the way how
why they are happening here um not just
in America but around our world. And so
it's so important for us to stay um
focused on what we need to stay focused
on. Keep studying our Bibles and
allowing the Holy Spirit to lead us into
all truth. Okay, we have greetings from
frosty white and cold Lach, Texas.
That's a lot to say for Texas. Texas is
always so hot. So if Texas is cold and
icy and snowy, then some of the other
parts of the country definitely are. But
welcome uh to Living Mana Church. Want
to welcome Katherine from Ohio. Good to
see you here. We are happy to have you
here uh at Living Mana Church. We have
Paul from uh Canada. Good to see you
here. Welcome uh to Living Man Mana
Church. And okay from Nambia Welves Bay,
welcome uh Elijah uh here to Living Mana
Church. Also, we have Coney Island in
New York, a first timer, Rose. Well, it
says Rose Folk. So, I I'm not quite sure
what your name is, but uh we are happy
to have you here for the first time at
Living Mana Church for you and all the
other first timers. Just want you to
know that we are 100% church that's 100%
online. We are here all throughout the
week. We have programming on mental
health on mental health on Mondays. Uh
we have physical health on Tuesdays. We
have two prayer services on Wednesday.
And I am going to share in a few moments
more about how to stay connected with
Living Mana Church and to be able to be
notified when these programs go live.
But we do welcome you here to Living
Mana Church. this is your first time and
I know there this is others first time
as well. Want to welcome um someone from
Barbados. Good to see you here at Living
Mana Church. All right, we have uh
Thomas from Madison, Alabama, just right
down the road from us. Always good to
see you here uh at Living Mana Church.
And it's so good uh just to have people
uh watching from all around the world,
all around America. We just welcome all
of you here to Living Mana Church.
Wanted to make a note. I was reminded to
be able to say this and I'll say it
today and to next week as well. We um
are in the process. We have a new
treasurer for Living Mana Church and she
is getting situated and we'll probably
bring her on just to introduce you guys
to um our our treasure and a new board
member for Living Mana Church. But just
with that, uh just letting you know that
so that um as she is getting settled and
getting everything um just um up to
speed, uh she will then be sending out
uh your tax receipts for the year of
2025 for your giving and donations to
Living Mana Church. So just wanted to to
let you guys know that and I will remind
you of that next week uh as well. want
to let you guys know how to stay
connected to Living Mana Church and how
we can actually stay connected to you as
well. Uh we want to to show share with
you how you are able to do that. If you
are here in North America, you will be
able to receive text alerts. And you can
sign up to do that by um just putting uh
the number 855207-4107
and um you can text LMC to that number
and that will automatically sign you up
to get text alerts. So, when we're going
live with our different programming,
when church service is 20 minutes uh out
and going to go live or if mental health
Mondays or true health Tuesday or our
prayer services or anything that we're
going live with, you will have 20 minute
notification to remind you that Living
Man Church is going live in just a short
time. That's if you live in North
America. If you live outside of North
America, which many of our viewing
audience and membership does live out of
North America, they live all around the
world, you're going to want to sign up
for Mighty Networks. I say it that way,
but then I have to always correct myself
and say everyone should sign up for
Mighty Networks because it is our
virtual church home for Living Manage
Church. People say, "How do you form
community or how do you uh connect with
people?" We can do that on Mighty
Networks because even though we're
virtual, we can connect there. You can
see all the small groups, all the
different uh small groups and ministries
that we have going on within the church.
You can see the leadership. You can
learn about them and you can decide
which one you may want to be a part of.
You will also get announcements and uh
be able to stay connected through mighty
networks if you are outside of the
country. Also want to remind you guys
that we do have children's programming.
It's Locosc
um goes live at 11:30 central time on
Zoom and you can text kids to 8552074107
and you can also email LMLC kids at
living.urch. The leadership will get
back with you if you are interested in
getting your kids signed up for LMOLC
kids. And so if you or someone you know
have children that would love to be a
part of that then please um just follow
that information. Also, Pastor Meyers
has virtual church office hours. Um and
so if you're needing to talk to Pastor
Meyers and needing to set up a time an
appointment time with him, please do
that by emailing patrice livingmana.live
and she will set that up for you. Also
want to let you guys know how if you are
wanting to become a member of Living
Mana Church, you can do that. And the
way that you're going to do that is use
that same email patrice at living
mana.live.
And if you are already a member, a
baptized member of the 7th Day Adventist
Church, you can transfer your membership
to Living Mana Church. You will use that
email. Patrice will get that ball
rolling for you. Uh and that's how
that's one way that you can become a
member of Living Mana Church. If you um
are already been baptized, don't feel
like you need to be baptized, but you'd
like to become a member of the 7th Day
Adventist Church and the me through
Living Mana Church, you can um come in
on Profession of Faith and you will use
that same email Patrice living mana.live
um and she will also start that process
for you as well. If you're wanting to
get baptized and to become a member of
the 7th Day Adventist Church and become
a member of living mana church, uh you
can do that and again you use the same
email patrice livingmana.live
um she will get that process started for
you and Pastor Meyers will be the one
that baptizes you if you want to be
baptized to become a member in that way.
Also just want to let you guys know a
little bit.
>> Hello. Hey LC family. This is Takara
here, your lead hangout host. And I am
inviting you to come and join me on
Hangouts. We get together on a Zoom. We
come together. We break out into
sessions, intimate groups of less than
10 or so. We're going to play games.
We're going to have um ice breakers.
We're going to have all kinds of things.
We're going to have a great time. Come
and join me and the rest of the hangout
hosts every other Sunday evening. Every
other Sunday evening, come hang out,
relax, enjoy. Invite a friend. Come and
have a good time. That's what it is
about hanging out. That's all it is. No
pressure. We We worship together, so
let's hang out together. And I hope to
see you at the next hangout. Love you
all.
Hangouts is such uh a blessing. So much
fun to do that. uh as a church family,
I've been able to attend several of
them, planning to be there, uh as many
as me and pastor can make it to, but
it's a great way to connect, have fun,
and just simply hang out together. So,
that is just an amazing thing that we
can do here at Living Mana Church. All
right. Want to um just let you guys uh
know about um let's see about Mana
connect newsletter. Want to let you guys
know about that. That is something new
that's uh been a blessing um here at
Living Mana Church. Let's see. Family, a
quick reminder that the next edition of
the Mana Connect newsletter letter drops
next week. If you haven't had a chance
to read the very first edition, we'd
love for you to check it out. The link
is in the chat. It also is available on
mighty networks or you can text in text
in to receive the link directly. Stay
connected, stay informed and stay
encouraged. Mana connect is your monthly
snapshot of everything happening across
living mana. So that helps to keep you
informed. It's such uh incredible
blessing um that the newsletter is. Also
want to remind you guys about give mana
that's led by sister Shaunene. Uh give
mana is our space on mighty networks
dedicated to outreach and inreach
ministry. It's designed to make
connecting with resources simple and
meaningful. Whether you're seeking help
offering support or pointing someone to
the right place in their local
community, find and coordinate local
resources, share guidance, and direct
others to support in their area.
Together, we make sure no one has to
walk alone. So that is Give Mana. And if
you want to be a part of that, just text
Mana to that 855 number that you see on
your screen. Okay. Hey, I want to tell
you guys about volunteers that are
needed here at Elos Church. But before I
do that, just want to let you guys know
that Mental Health Monday is coming back
this Monday at 700 p.m. uh Central
Standard Time. Dr. Ricardo White and
myself will be hosting um a new uh live
uh mental health Monday. So definitely
uh sign up to get those text alerts so
you can be reminded when we go live and
that you can uh be a part of that and
you will not miss out on that timely
information. All right, just want to um
just want to tell you guys about the
volunteers that are needed. Uh Elos Kids
is definitely one of those areas. Uh,
Sister Tanya has put out uh an SOS. Our
children's ministry needs additional
volunteers to support our growing group
of little ones. That's a blessing to
know that we have so many little kids
joining. If you have a heart uh for
teaching, serving, and simply helping
create a safe, joyful space for our
kids, this is a great place to plug in.
And I will just let you know that um
there is a process. Um for those parents
who are hearing this like not just
anybody can work with our children. They
are special uh to us and um we have um a
standard and a process that if you are
going to be a part of volunteering to
help with the kids, you do have to go
through um a process of uh where you are
cleared to be able to work with
children. So just to just to uh let the
parents and those uh other adults that
may be wondering uh not just anyone can
work with our kids but we are looking
forward to the ones who God wants and
are able to clear that process to be
able to help with our kids. Also want to
remind you of the benevolence committee.
Our benevolence team is also seeking
committed volunteers to help review
requests, coordinate, support, and serve
our community with compassion and
integrity. Uh so we're also needing um
volunteers for the benevolence committee
as well and um that is so very
important. Also the glow group host we
are expanding our digital small groups
and need more hosts to help lead
conversations build community and to
create welcoming spa spaces for
fellowship and growth. If you are ready
to serve or want to learn more, visit
the service opportunity section in
Mighty Networks. Every hand makes a
difference and there's a place prepared
for you to serve. So, we are uh looking
forward uh to that. Also, for you guys
to be a part of that. Also, just wanting
to remind you guys about our LMOC
YouTube growth. Um, and you probably
have seen that we have um our numbers on
you YouTube have gone up uh
significantly. Let's let me tell you all
about that. From October to December,
our YouTube channel exploded with
growth. Subscribers surged from 7,000 to
46,000 views skyrocketed from 300,000 to
2.9 million. This is this isn't just
numbers. It's impact. This is real
measurable growth. And the beauty is you
can track it for yourself. Every
donation you make has a direct uh
visible impact. You're not just giving.
You are fueling results and can actually
watch and unfold in real time. In the
past uh even our most popular sermons
average of 1500 to 2,000 views. With our
view with our new strategy uh those same
sermons are reaching 150,000 to 200,000
views. Our reach has gone by more than
10 has grown, excuse me, by more than
tenfold. In fact, closer to a hundfold.
And these aren't just Adventist views
viewers. We're reaching the unchurched
and and non-believers. People who may be
hearing the gospel for the first time.
Why does this matter? You may be asking.
Nearly a quarter of a million people uh
watch sermons on hellfire and Sabbath.
Our content is showing up in feeds like
digital track and the numbers prove they
are clicking, watching, and engaging.
The challenge ahead, we're aiming for
10,000 new subscribers every month,
reaching 150,000 subscribers by next
year. Imagine the lives touched if we
can sustain that pace. Why we need you.
Strategic marketing has fueled this
growth, but it isn't free. Here's the
difference your giving makes. For every
$1 spent, dozens of people hear the
gospel. A gift of a $100 helps us reach
thousands of viewers with truthfilled
content. Your donation to the local
budget is an investment in souls
reached, sermons heard, and truth shared
across the globe.
So, we are uh just looking forward to
just continuing to grow our YouTube
channel um even more. We praise God for
uh this possibility and the way we're
able to reach the world. So if you are
wanting to give and support, please
follow um by we're going to talk about
how to give through Adventist giving. So
when you are able to to give and want to
be able to do that through Adventist
giving, please think about how our
advertising and how we are growing on
YouTube. Also just want to remind you
guys about LMLC Global. Uh that is
another way that we are going into all
the world. We are currently able to go
into seven different languages. And if
you are here for the first time, we want
to just show you a sneak peek on what
that looks like.
Kindche.
always a blessing. Even though we talk
about this each and every week so that
you guys are just reminded of what we
are able to do with LMLC Global, it's
still so amazing that we can be able to
go into all of the world right now in
seven different languages. We'd like to
grow that even more. So when you are
giving through Adventist giving to our
local church budget, please keep in mind
LMLC Global as we continue to go into
all the world and right now in seven
different languages um um uh in the
world. And so to be able to continue to
give or to support giving for the first
time, you can go to Adventist giving and
there you will put an uh living mana
church and on the right hand corner a
virtual tithe envelope will drop down
and you will see there where you can
give your tithe which your tithe tithe
supports northeastern conference. Living
mounted church is uh a church that is a
part of the northeastern conference and
that helps to support the worldwide 7th
day avenous church as well. And when you
give to the local church budget that
helps us to continue to do what we are
doing here at Living Manage Church um
and that is what as they used to say
like well even here I guess it helps
here too keeps the lights on if you will
that is where we are able to do
everything that living mana church does
I would say locally but we're globally
too so it's what helps us to be able to
do everything that we're doing also you
will see there other areas the
benevolence f fund is a place that you
can give as well. That helps us to be
able to help others that reach out to
the church that are needing some
financial assistance, we would take it
from that area um of our local church
budget. And you'll be able to see so
many other areas to where you can give
there. If giving online is not uh what
you would like to do, if you would like
to mail in a check with your tithe um
and with your um with your offering, we
will be able to process that for you and
you will be able to mail it to the PO
box that you see there on your screen,
the address that is there. Um, and if
you would just please send a note with
uh the check that you are mailing in to
let us know how much is for tithe that
will support the northeastern conference
and the worldwide church and then how
much is for the local church budget that
again will help support what living mana
church is doing um all around the world.
But what we're doing here with our um
again I want to say local church but
we're not a local church. We're an
international church, but that's what
helps us to be able to do what we do
here at Living Mana Church. Just want to
say thank you to you guys because your
prayers, your uh just support by just
showing up and sharing, liking,
subscribing, inviting people to church,
your financial gifts, all of that is
what helps keeps uh Living Mana Church
going. And again, we will be four years
old on April 9th. That's our
anniversary. the church is almost four
years old. And it is such a blessing to
see how God has led this church year
after year. How um he brings just the
right people to come and to help support
the church to give their talents and
their gifts to make the church what it
is. And so we are just so very thankful
to you. So I'm thanking you and I'd like
for you to join me as we thank God for
all his many blessings to all of us. If
you please bow your heads with me as I
pray.
Heavenly Father, Lord, I thank you for
this Sabbath, Lord. I thank you for this
church and just the blessing. Again, I
say this all the time and I God, you
know, I mean it uh from the bottom of my
heart, but it's been such a blessing to
me and to my husband and to our family.
Uh living, we love living mana church.
We love the people. We love just uh what
we're able to do through this church to
be able to reach so many people around
the world. So, I thank you and I praise
you, God. Lord, I praise you for all of
our volunteers and our staff that are
here that work with Living Manage Church
to really make Living Manage Church
work. I say it all the time. This is not
a me and Pastor Meyers um program
because
we can't do and have the impact by
ourselves um of what Living Matter
Church is having all around the world.
And so, we're just so thankful for the
team. Lord, people have come today to
church. They've come broken. Some some
are rejoicing and praising you because,
you know, everything is going okay. And
others are just barely making it here.
They are going through so much. And
Lord, I lift them up to you, Lord. I
don't know their personal story. I don't
know exactly what they're going through,
but they have a burden on their heart.
Lord, they may have just lost a loved
one and they are grieving. I pray and
ask that you will comfort them and give
them peace even through this difficult
time. Lord, I pray for all of the
marriages that are represented here
today. Lord, I know oh so well as a
therapist what marriages go through and
even I've been married 27 years. I know
the ups and the downs. Lord, everybody
goes through those. And so I pray um for
those who are going through hard times
in their marriage. Lord, we've raised
four adult children. We know the ups and
downs of that. And so I pray for those
who are going through uh issues with
their either adult children or teenage
or young children. Every aspect of
parenting no matter what phase they are
in. I pray for them in their situation.
Lord um I know those there's some that
are just burdened with health or they
have a family member that is going
through a health issue. Lord, I pray for
heal healing over the ones that are sick
and I pray for emotional support for
those who have to take care of them or
be their emotional support. Lord, Lord,
I know there's others that are going
through financial burdens um and they
just don't they don't see any light out
of the darkness of their financial
issues. I pray that you will work a
miracle in their situation. Lord,
nothing is too hard for you. Money is no
big deal to you. you can provide for
them by giving money or working things
out in another way. Lord, I just pray
that you will um just intervene in their
situation, Lord. And lastly, I I just
want to lift up Pastor Meyers as he has
a message from you, Lord. You have given
something that he has worked on and you
put you've put it on his heart. So, I
pray that he will deliver that message
to all of us. Um and it will touch our
hearts in a special way today. Lord, I
praise you and I thank you just for who
you are. And I ask all of these things
in Jesus name. Amen.
There is nothing you cannot do with God.
No matter who you are, where you come
from, what your past may be, you were
made for more.
This new road set before you, God
already has a plan for this season of
life you're walking through. Jesus wants
to walk with you. This is your moment to
do more than you have ever imagined. The
more that God has prepared for you, more
of his presence, more of his goodness,
more of his kindness, more of his peace,
more of his joy, more of his power,
breaking through ordinary circumstances
with extraordinary strength. More of him
so when you stand before your Goliath,
you don't shake with fear, but have more
strength in your spirit and more courage
in your bones. more of him. So when
seasons of darkness surround you, you
can declare more of his promises over
your life, more of his presence filling
you, more of his Holy Spirit walking
with you. Jesus is calling you to more
of him each and every day. So stand up
in your spirit. Put on the full armor of
God. Declare with authority that Jesus
is more than enough. Speak it over your
life, over your family's life, over your
future. Make this the declaration that
marks the next chapter of your
incredible story that you were made for
more.
What's up everybody? for Brotherhood
Music. Massive shout out to Elevate
Studios for having us here to check out
the song called Open Week Eyes. We pray
and hope that it blesses you guys out
there as much as it blesses us.
Open the eyes of my heart. Lord,
open the eyes of my heart.
I want to see you.
Open the eyes of my heart, Lord.
Open the eyes of my heart.
I want to see you.
I want to see
you.
To see you. High lifted
up.
Shining in the light of your glory.
Pour out your power and love
as we sing. Holy, holy,
holy
to see you. I lift it up.
Shining in the light of your glory.
Pour out your power and love
as we sing. Holy, holy, holy.
I want to see
you.
Open the eyes of my heart, Lord.
Open the eyes of my heart.
I want to see
you.
Open the eyes of my heart, Lord.
Just open the eyes of my heart.
I want to see.
I want to see
you. Oh, to see you. I lift it up. Yeah.
Shining in the light of your glory.
Pour out, pour out your power and love
as we sing. Holy, holy,
holy to see you high and lifted
up. Oh,
shining in the light of your glory.
Pour out, pour out your power and love
as we sing. Holy, holy,
holy, holy,
holy.
I want to see
you.
Here at Living Mana, we bear each
other's burdens. When you need support
or prayer, when you're feeling
discouraged
or alone or anxious,
you don't have to face life struggles
alone.
Let us come boldly unto the throne of
grace that we may obtain mercy and find
grace to help in our time of need.
The Lord is close to the brokenhearted
and saves those who are crushed in
spirit.
Amen. Amen. Greeting, greetings, saints
of the most high God. Welcome to another
edition of living manners prayer and
praise time. I am brother Cherry and I'm
here as always with my lovely bride
Amra. Want to send out a shout out of
love to everybody. So glad to be here
with you all uh worshiping and
fellowshipping and just listening to the
word of God and looking at your prayer
requests go up in the chat. We're happy
to be able to serve you this way. We
thank God for the opportunity.
Um, wow. Everybody, you know, we we're
always by the time we get here for
prayer in the prayer segment, we're
we're just so excited. Um, and our
hearts are just swelling just from the
things that we're hearing and things
we're hearing from you in the chat,
things we're hearing from pastor and
first lady. I want I want to share a
thought I had with you today before we
do some shout outs and some hellos and
some praise reports and then we'll go to
the altar. but um to the throne. But um
in Luke chap
21 25 and 26, you're familiar with this
word. And as I listen to all of the
stuff that's going on in the world
today, I want you to think about
something. Bible says, "There shall be
signs in the sun and in the moon and in
the stars and upon the earth, distress
of nations with perplexity and the sea
and the waves roaring."
>> We know what the sea and the waves
represent in prophecy. just people,
multitudes of people and tongues and
nations roaring, something going on
amongst people. And then in verse 26,
the Lord says, "Men's hearts failing
them for fear and for looking after
those things which are coming on the
earth. For the powers of heaven shall be
shaken."
>> You know, pastor said it this morning.
You know, there's so much going on, you
don't know what to grab hold to. I mean,
this is happening. By the time you get
your mind around that, something else
happening over here. By the time you get
your mind around that, something else is
happening over here. And obviously, we
can't bury our heads in the sand and act
like all this stuff's not going on or we
don't notice it. We do. But I tell you,
saints, it is the word of the living God
that is able to build us up, strengthen
us, and allow us to take possession of
our inheritance. It gives us rest in the
middle of the storm. That's what the
word of God does. It's powerful. And we
have to get the word in our hearts. And
so if you want to cleave to something,
cleave to the word of the living God.
That's why we encourage you this
morning. Binge watch. Uh, you know, and
not just, you know, you're going to get
into your personal studies, but I want
to encourage you to ben watch. Binge
watch back to basics. Matthew 24,
Elephant in the room, the story of the T
horns. Pastor going to do a part two.
Get that stuff in. And as pastor told
you with us when he first shared it,
you're going to see things and hear
things that perhaps he didn't hear or
see. You know, this this truth is from
the mind of the infinite God. And so
each of us are individuals and we have
unique individuality and relationships
with God. And so when you when you get
into the word, God gonna say something
to you and you gonna come back and be
able to bless and edify the church. So
we that's what our one of our biggest
prayers is. Lord, open the eyes of all
of our hearts. that we might see you and
only you can see from your perspective
and come back and share. We're looking
at the same thing, but we're here to
build one another up. Iron sharpen and
iron. And so, just wanted to give you
that word of encouragement. Settle down
into the word of God. All that stuff
that's going on out there, it's going to
happen. It's going to happen. The devil
is trying to make us drink water from a
fire hose.
>> And that's not what we going to do. So,
we're not gonna be trying to fix all
this stuff and get our mind around all
this stuff because that's what the
scripture says. Men's hearts are going
to be failing them looking at that stuff
because it's overwhelming. Yeah.
>> But when you get in the word of God and
he tells you, "Behold, you are of the
household of David, it has been
prophesied over your life that you're
going to grow stronger and stronger in
the fruit of the spirit and in love and
in victory and that the house of Saul, I
don't care what they're up to, are going
to grow weaker and weaker." Somebody
shout hallelujah in this place this
morning. We ought to give God glory and
praise because yes, we it's prophesied
over our life that we're going to become
stronger and stronger. You saw that
yourself last Sabbath. If you're like
me, you probably saw it about five or
six more times this week because I put
that thing on repeat. And so, just be
encouraged, saints of the most high God,
stand strong in the victory that Christ
Jesus has purchased for us with his shed
blood. Can we say amen, somebody?
>> Amen.
>> All right, Sister Sharon Faith Johns, I
see you in the chat. Sister Cuda from
from from Walrus Bay, Nambia. I'm gonna
shout you out here in a minute. Sister,
you and and your daughter Hadassa,
brother Elijah. Love y'all watching from
all the way around the world. I know
y'all working with that time zone. But
listen, we love y'all and love having
you here with us today. And everybody,
y'all know the regulars. Y'all know I
want to shout y'all out, right? Hey
everybody. Okay, but there's some new
there's some newcomers here. First
timers here. Frederick the Great. I
greeted you in the chat. Welcome to
Living Mana. Uh, Rose Folks from Coney
Island, New York. Welcome, welcome,
welcome. Marian Anna
Celo, I believe that's your name. I know
you're from New Mexico. You're here with
us. Greetings, greetings, greetings. I'm
sorry if I butchered your name there. I
couldn't quite see what I was reading,
but love you and thank you so much for
joining us. And brother Ruben
or is it Ryan? Okay, Ryan is here. Ryan
is here and Ruben, both of you are here.
And so want to want to want to greet you
and say welcome to Living Mana. We all
send you a a great shout out. Say thank
you for joining us today. We love y'all.
And um I don't know what else I wanted
to say. I wanted to shout somebody else
out. Oh,
the storm attendees are here today
because I'm looking the numbers are up,
right? Our numbers were up quite a bit.
So those of you who are here because you
had storms at your church, welcome.
We're glad to have you. Love your
support. I know some of you usually
watch later, but thank God for you and
we do we do love you and give God praise
for you being here.
>> Amen.
>> All right. What else?
>> You know, I wanted to first off, I'm
shouting out everyone in the chat. I
don't have time to go through the full
roll call, but we see your welcomes and
greetings and we love you so much. So,
thank you so much. But,
>> you know, I was um listening to your
introduction
And it also reminds me if you all have a
chance to attend Dr. White's mastermind
institute talk on heaven.
>> Oh man,
>> we attended that last night and this
time that we're experiencing here in the
world is such a blip in time.
>> Yeah. And it was such an amazing
perspective of forever that we have to
look forward to. If we focus on God,
just like you said, we have thousands
and thousands upon thousands of years of
living without pain and sorrow and
frustration and and sin. And so,
>> yeah,
>> it was just such an amazing time last
year. I want to say Dr. White has some
interesting thoughtprovoking principles
from the word of God all based on the
word of God to to maybe some things that
we haven't really looked at and
considered about heaven and the
experience of heaven. You know,
sometimes we get this false concept
about what heaven's going to be like.
But I'm going to tell you something. We
were really impressed last night by the
spirit of God. And I think those things
that he was sharing are things that are
designed to take our minds, you know,
away from some of that stuff that can
cause us to be overwhelmed or distracted
here. God has given us something to look
forward to when he tells us, "Look,
we're pressing forward toward the mark
for the prize of the high calling of God
in Christ Jesus." God has given us
something to look forward to. And so I I
really, if you get a chance, Dr. White's
considering how they're going to share
it and what platform they want to share
it on, but I think it's a it's a
powerful.
>> Yeah, you can look him up online at the
Mastermind Institute and he usually has
all of his stuff there.
>> Amen. Amen. Beautiful.
>> All right. Are we ready?
>> Yes.
>> For
some announcements.
>> There was somebody I wanted to say hey
to Sister Sheila. God bless you. Thank
you so much. Sister Sheila's collecting
all these prayer requests in the chat if
if we happen to miss any because I I saw
her early and I wanted to shout her out.
Sister Sheila, love you, beautiful
sister.
>> I want to shout out Denise because we
got some special fellowship time this
morning. So, love you so much, sis.
>> Yeah, I thought I heard that. And Sister
Pauline, here we go with the roll.
>> I didn't mean to start it. Well, now you
started it.
>> It's on now. Okay. So, so Pauline, love
you. My sister, pray for you and your
family. Seriously. And uh, brother Elder
Robert, we love you and all of you.
Brother Tennessee, love you, my man. God
bless you. Happy Sabbath. And I just
want to, let me just throw umbrella out
there. All the beautiful godly women of
living mana. And maybe you're visitor
women of God. We love you. Remnant women
and visitors. Love y'all. Y'all are
doing an amazing work. I am continue to
be uh amazed and inspired by our
beautiful women of God.
>> Amen. All right. Before I go into the
praise reports, I have some
announcements. If you would like to
submit a prayer request or a praise
report that we will pray on throughout
the week and that I can share your
praise report here on the broadcast,
please send an email to pray
living mana.urch.
If you would like to join us on the
prayer team, we are always needing new
prayer team members.
Um, please also send an email to pray at
livingmana.urch.
It's an amazing amazing ministry and
it's been such a blessing to us. If you
are requesting a special ops prayer team
for yourself or a loved one, please send
an email to spec ops, that's sops
at living manana.urch
and that's more detailed prayer that
happens um frequently for specific
situations.
If you are needing a midweek pickup,
please join us for Power Wednesday every
Wednesday at 4:30 p.m. Pacific Standard
Time, 6:30 Central, and 7:30 Eastern
Standard Time, followed by the Power
Line where um we take live prayer
requests and that is every Wednesday at
6:00 PM right after power Wednesday
Pacific Standard Time, 8:00 p.m. Central
900 p.m. Eastern Standard Time.
If you would like to join the women's
ministry
on Mighty Networks, please send an email
to women at living manana.urch.
Now that I'm talking about the women's
ministry, we have a special event coming
up called the ladies lounge. You're
invited to our ladies lounge, a special
women's ministry gathered centered
around our Amazing Grace devotional
monthly summary. This is more than a
meeting. It's a moment to pause,
reflect, and be reminded that God's
grace is still meeting us right where we
are. We'll spend time sharing insights
from this month's devotional,
encouraging one another, and celebrating
what God is doing in our lives. And yes,
there will be fun, laughter, and games
because sisterhood should feel joyful,
not heavy. Whether you're joining from
your phone, tablet, or laptop, this is a
safe, welcoming space for women of all
ages. Real conversation, real
connection, and real encouragement. So,
grab your favorite drink, get
comfortable, and come lounge with us.
And that is happening this Thursday,
January 29th at 8:00 p.m. Eastern
Standard Time, 5:00 p. p.m. Pacific
Standard Time. Um, so yes, please
join the women's ministry and attend
this awesome event.
>> Yeah.
>> If you would like to join the men's
ministry,
um, please send an email to
menlivingmana.urch.
And I think this is important for all
men to connect. They have specific
issues and trials they go through as men
and I think they need to be supported
because well there are spiritual
leaders.
>> Amen.
>> All right.
Praise reports.
>> Um
>> Oh, did you want to say something?
>> Yeah, just one more thing. Um,
thank you. beautiful job with the
announcements. I just want to say one
more thing. Um the prayer ministry is
getting ready to launch these breakout
rooms. We actually already have launched
them, but there's a breakout room
ministry that's going to be something
something else. And uh keep us in prayer
as God uh continues to allow us to, you
know, listen to see what he's saying and
to follow his lead. I love that we have
uh uh beautiful sisters and brothers who
are going to be getting involved.
Particularly sister Valerie is going to
be leading up a lot in that and we'll
have her on. She'll do some talking
about it. We'll be talking about it
during power Wednesday. But uh our
breakout rooms is where we give an have
take an opportunity to just get
oneonone. Maybe you want to step aside
and have some private one-on-one time.
someone who knows how to listen, someone
who knows how to uh uh be uh have
compassion and uh you know, who knows
how to just help you carry your burden
through the storm and you might need
some of that. And uh we want to be
making ourselves available to you uh if
you're hurting and you just need a
shoulder to lean on, you know, and we
want to be there for you in every way we
can. A little more intimate way is what
these breakout rooms are about. So, uh
praise God for that.
>> All right. I think you're speaking about
just in case anyone's confused about
breakout rooms that's on Zoom in
our power Wednesday.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
First praise report coming from Zadwa
Malangu. Hello Zodwa.
I want to thank God for coming through
for my daughter. She passed her GCSEs.
Thank you for your prayers. God bless
your ministry.
>> Amen to that.
from Jamie Ael. Hello Jamie.
>> Hello.
>> Family. God really answers prayers. On
Christmas Eve, my neighbor was admitted
to the hospital. He had open heart
surgery. Together with his family, we
prayed for his deliverance. He's home
now. Praise God for that.
>> Amen.
>> From Francis Grant.
with a trusting heart in holding on to
Jesus. I want to thank all the prayer
warriors for lifting me and my husband
up to the Lord.
>> Tonight, my husband was told by the Lord
to take his rest. By God's mercy and
grace, he is sleeping and waiting for
the trumpet sound to awake. Please
remember our children and grandchildren
in a special way as they come to grips
with Pop Pop being gone. My heart is sad
but at peace for my husband no longer
has to deal with the pain and challenges
he endured due to all the medical
conditions he faced. The Lord never
makes a mistake and I am leaning on his
arms of grace. Again, thank you for your
support and prayers. Also, please
continue to pray for the family as
Randy, my nephew's funeral service is on
Monday bearing the winter storms coming
to New Jersey.
>> Amen. Amen. Francis, we will definitely
be keeping you in prayer.
From Lawrence Nagi,
after one garage told us they weren't
interested in repairing our car, after a
second garage told us it was a ride-off,
but wanted to buy it from us for a
pittance to repair and resell it. After
two accidents on the same day, people
damaging the bodywork, our God had
mercy. He guided us to someone working
in a garage that only changed tires and
did oil changes, but who not only
determined the problem, but took it upon
himself to make the repair. Who would
have thought? These were only these were
there were other miracles, but I won't
bore you any longer. Definitely not
boring.
>> Just thank you for your precious
prayers. Praise his great name. Praise
God, Lawrence. That's amazing.
>> Amen. Amen. And never feel that your
praise reports are boring. Your miracles
are never boring. Uh your story is a
message to somebody. Somebody needs to
hear what you're going through and what
God's doing for you.
>> Amen. And finally, from Hope, who has
been going through an illness, she says,
"I'm doing pretty well. I've got
antibiotics that I've got to take for 10
days. I'm just on my second day of them,
but I'm believing that God's got this
and this infection is going to go away.
Thank you so much for praying for me
>> and hope we will continue to keep you in
our prayers.
Um, but that is the praise reports for
this week. Please don't forget to submit
your praise reports. Um, we all love to
hear what God is doing in your life.
>> Amen. Amen. Praise the Lord. And now,
saints, we're going to prepare to go to
the throne of grace and seek God's face
in prayer this morning. Um, but before
we do, I just wanted to there's a couple
of uh uh
praise uh prayer prayer requests that
came in and and then some people that I
specifically want to shout out sister
Zakara. We are continuing to pray for
you and your family, the Jenkins family,
that um y'all will be strong, that you
be strong, you be a light there, my
sister. Keep your head up and uh
continue to press on. God is God is
able. Hold on to the word he's given you
for your life. Don't let it go. Don't
let it go. Uh also uh this beautiful
sister from um um Nambia Walis Bay and
she's at Wawas Bay 7th Day Adventist
Church there and uh she's leading the
youth and she's looking uh asking God to
give her uh business opportunities to
help to relieve the financial uh burden
in her life. She's watching today with
her beautiful daughter Adessa and her
son Elijah. Elijah has a cough. Elijah,
we're praying for that little cough,
young man. and but uh Cuda Washa
Tarravinga, I love saying your name.
Cudawasha Tyrainga, we we love you. We
thank you for joining us and we're
definitely praying that you'll be able
to manage the time zone. We know that's
uh been a challenge for y'all, but
you're here and we thank God for you and
we keeping you lifted up in prayer. Love
you so much. And also one of you guys
remember sister um the M&M's one of the
M&M's not Melinda but Michaela who uh uh
they let out when we had our youth do
the Sabbath and Michaela did the
announcements for first lady. Well
Michaela her mother Carrie Jano you know
her and her sister Jocelyn and her
husband Mike. Well they're praying and
and you know they're dealing with
something right now that's really it's a
blessing and it's also a challenge. U
Michaela is traveling to Australia. It's
her first time traveling, but she's
going to arise there for three months.
And so, uh, we want to pray for
traveling mercies. We want to pray for
protection for her. Want to pray that
the Lord continues to work, uh, as he
has been working marvelously in her
young life that she'll grow closer
closer to Jesus, you know, and this
experience would just be so amazing for
her. And and we want to pray for Carrie,
you know, her mom because it's going to
be difficult for her with Michaela's
first time traveling. And uh and so
Carrie, if you're watching, I know you
are. I saw you there in the chat. We
love you and we continue to pray for
you. We thank you for the wonderful,
wonderful contribution to the kingdom of
God. You and your family are so special
to us. We will be keeping you in prayer
always, always.
And so more prayer requests. Uh Sister
Marisella Johnson reminded us to keep
those people in prayer who are in the
wake of the storms, the winter storms in
North Carolina, South Carolina
particularly. Christie, we we saw your
prayer request for South Carolina. I
spoke with my mom last night. She's
there. I'll be calling her in just a bit
by the grace of God. Make sure she's
okay. Also, we saw um uh Laya, Sister
Laya uh in North Carolina. We're praying
for you and Brother Wes and that you all
will be safe there and stay warm in
Jesus name. And you know, Sister
Marisella reminded us that there are
homeless people out there. There pets
out there. There are animals out there.
There people that are traveling out
there. Uh we want to pray God provide
protection for everybody. We're praying
also for sister Pauline, her
granddaughter, her granddaughter's
friend um uh uh Shazam. We're praying
for her and just praying that, you know,
that they will be blessed and that they
will be able to deal with some of this
issues that young people are going
through right now. Sister Angela
reminded us to pray about ICE. We've
been seeing so many different stories
>> uh and watching some of the stuff that's
been going on there. Lord have mercy and
help uh people dealing with that that
that that that uh oh man I don't really
know how to describe it but it's it's a
horrible experience for a lot of people
seeing people literally are shot and
losing their lives in this thing. Um
sister Christina is um reminding us to
pray for sister Francis Grant and her
family as you just heard the praise
report and Francis Grant spoke about her
husband who has fallen asleep in Jesus.
We're praying for the grandkids and
everyone
>> and her nephew.
>> And her nephew. Amen. Thank you, my
love. Uh Ayana, we're praying for your
client who lost someone who's been a
father to them and and it's been pretty
devastating to her. So, we're continuing
to pray. As we mentioned earlier, we're
praying for Takara uh and the uh Jenkins
family, her uncle Mark specifically, and
um I believe her um parish. Uh there
were some issues there. We're praying
about all those details. Um, Mimi Moore
is asking for uh her work is uh a
workman's comp case and so we're praying
that God will grant her relief and come
through for her. Um, Pauline has
reminded us to pray for Dakota who had
cancer and had surgery and uh him and
his wife and his family are dealing with
some struggles uh you know financial
struggles as a result of that. I believe
there's been some separation there and
they're doing some counseling. So, we're
praying for them. Also, MT is asking for
God's leading in the year 2026. Um, she
has some visions and she has some plans
and and and just asking God just guide
guide MT in these plans and and guide
her in her in her life throughout the
year. Baby girl 6102 has a friend named
Caitlyn who just became interested in
the Lord and she wants to pray that
those seeds will fall on good ground and
that uh the enemy won't be able to come
and snatch them out of her heart. And I
want to pray that for a lot of you who
are sharing with others who have become
interested in the word of the Lord and
beginning to ask questions and you've
been studying and want to be able to
give those answers. So, we love you so
much. You're more than welcome, Sister
Carrie. Amen. Love you. I see your
message in the chat. Tracy L112
has a job that's ending soon and wants
to pray for employment. Lord knows we
know what that's about and we're more
than happy to pray for you. But let me
tell you something. You get in the Bible
and you speak the word of the Lord, your
emotions will get involved. Sometimes
it's going to look hard. It going to
look a little scary. He's always Oh,
listen. Some of y'all know he is an
ontime God. I'll tell you right now,
he's an ontime God. And he he may not
come with you when you want him, but
he'll be there right on time. If he hold
up your blessing today, it's because he
want to double it up tomorrow. God
cannot fail somebody. God cannot fail.
So, let yourself be in alignment with
him. Speak what he says. uh stand on
what he says. No matter what you're
going through, trust in him. He will
come through. Hallelujah.
Man, I I I want I wanted to feel that.
>> Amen. Amen. And so, anyway, we also want
to pray uh Zebed Grace Grace. Hello,
Zebed Grace has reminded us today to
pray for widows and orphans. And thank
God for putting that on your heart,
praying for widows and orphans. And God,
give us the words. Give us the
sensitivity, the empathy to understand
the need to pray for the He's a father
to the fatherless. Amen. And I know
he'll be a husband to those who are are
waiting and are lonely and and grieving
and going through that process of of
healing. So, thank God for you. And uh,
Brother Spamco Pulk, we are definitely
going to pray for those who are
receiving the books that you're passing
out and the literature that you're
passing out. We're still praying about
everything in your life and considering
that support being. We we we remember
that. We're praying for that. And we're
praying for your daughter that she will
receive the Lord Jesus Christ. There's a
promise that the Lord gave me earlier in
the week as we're praying for children
and youth. In Psalm 115:14, he says,
"The Lord shall increase you more and
more, you and your children. Stand on
that, beloved, as the Lord converts your
children and they speak with the enemy
in the gate." Let us go to the throne of
grace.
>> Couple more.
>> Amen. Amen. Anetta Carr, remember me,
Brother Terry. Need transfusion
urgently.
>> Oh, Sister Anetta, absolutely.
>> Oscar Rodriguez is asking for prayer for
his ex-girlfriend's faith. And Renee,
12, please pray for my friend Monica.
Her son, 15year-old Amari, is in the
hospital with liver failure. Please pray
for healing and strength for them and
the medical staff.
And I'm not sure what Reed, sorry, the
comments come down so quickly, so we
apologize. Terry picked up as many as he
could. Um, from Reed W. Not sure what
the prayer request was for, but it's for
his family.
>> Okay. Definitely. Definitely.
Definitely. Yeah, there are a lot of
them. And I want to I want to assure you
of one thing. I know this. I'm a living
witness. I say this. I know that the
Lord hears and answers your prayers.
>> He is able to do exceeding abundantly
above anything we ask or think. He knows
about when we stretch forth our hands
says, "Lord, help us with all these
needs and all these prayer requests,
whether we speak them specifically or
not, we are joining in faith with you
sincerely from the heart, beloved." And
God is more than able. He knows. He
knows and he hears and he answers. Trust
me, I'm I would not I would not tell you
I I know this if I didn't know this. I I
I sometimes tease with him when I
brothers and sisters when I tell them I
know what it's like to be below the
bottom looking up at the bottom. And the
Lord did not consider that too low for
him to reach. So no matter what you're
going through, he is able somebody and
you all ought to put that in the chat as
we go to the throne of grace. God, we
know you are able to save, heal, touch,
and deliver. And so, Father, we come
before you in faith today, Lord. From
Genesis to Revelation, we've seen
promise after promise after promise. You
have never spoken a word, Lord, that is
not create anointed with your creative
power. You are able, oh God, to to to
save from the from the utter from the
gutmost to the uttermost. Someone has
said, Lord, you're able, oh God, to do
anything but fail. God, thank you that
you are greater than every need. Every
medical need, every emotional need,
every psychological need, every
financial need. Lord God, you're able to
heal cost today. You're able to provide
blood transfusions. Some of us know that
spiritually because you have changed us
and transformed us and took that stony
heart out of our chest and put within us
a heart of flesh. Hallelujah. And you
have washed us in the blood of Jesus. Oh
God, you do heart transfusions, blood
transfusions, liver transfusions, mind
transfu formations and transfusions. You
change it all. You've made us a new
creation in Christ Jesus. And here on
this blessed Sabbath day, Lord, that you
have sanctified and set apart. We come
into your glorious presence, oh God,
looking at you, the divine creator of
heaven and earth. You are the most high
God, possessor of heaven and earth. You
have subdued our enemies under our feet.
And because of that, we come before you
and we bow and worship today. We give
you praise and glory and honor today,
Lord. We enter into rest today by faith,
God, because your works have been
finished from before the foundation of
the world. Lord, we only ask pour your
spirit upon us. Open our eyes that we
might see what you have already
accomplished. That our lips may give you
glory and give you praise. that we might
offer up the sacrifices and praise unto
you because you cannot fail because your
word will not return unto you void. You
said that your word workketh effectually
in those who believe. Lord, we believe
today. Help our unbelief. Oh God,
manifest your glory upon us. Manifest
your miracle working power in and
through our life so that we might give
glory and honor. Don't let the enemy
defeat our mind. Don't let the enemy
rejoice over your inheritance today, oh
Lord, in Jesus name. Not for our sake,
not for any righteousness that we have
done. For we are unworthy, oh God, but
for your name's sake, because we are
your people called by your name. We have
none in heaven, Lord, that we desire
beside you. We have no hope in this
world other than you, oh God.
Hallelujah. Everything in this world is
passing away, oh Lord. Nothing in this
world that we can rely on and can depend
on. And so on this Sabbath day, we press
forward toward the mark. We come boldly
to the throne of grace. God, we humble
our hearts before you, oh Lord. We plead
the blood of Jesus and ask that you wash
us, cleanse us, Lord God. Purify our
mind, oh Lord. Remove everything within
us that's standing between us and you
standing between us in the realization
of the fact that victory is ours in
Jesus. You said this is the victory that
overcometh the world, even our faith.
And so we pray, Lord, it is not even the
earnestness of our prayer. It is not
even Lord if I sat here and prayed all
night long God if I wrestled Lord God
until the breaking of day oh God it is
nothing to do what I do but it is your
faithfulness hallelujah it is your
goodness oh God it is because you have
promised and you will not fail and so we
give you the glory the honor and praise
that you have heard these prayer
requests oh God and you're more than
able to answer them Lord you're not a
man that you should lie ne you the son
of man that you would repent from the
words that have gone forth from your
mouth, Lord. You said, "Whosoever shall
call upon your name shall be saved."
Those words have gone forth from your
mouth, Father. You cannot lie. You're
perfect and do not need to lie. You've
anointed your word. Your word is alive.
And once you have spoken it, it's gone
to do what you said it's going to do.
It, hallelujah, shall accomplish that
which you have sent it forth to do. Not
me, Lord. Not no one else but you, oh
God. And for that we give you glory,
honor, and praise. And so Lord, in the
name of Jesus, stretched forth thy
mighty hand to work miracles, signs, and
wonders in in the lives of those who
have put their hope in you today.
Everyone watching, everyone within the
sound of my voice today, who putting
their hope in you, putting their trust
in you, putting their faith in you,
those you have known from before the
foundation of the world. Lord, we give
you praise today. And Lord, I don't mean
to go on and on and on, but Lord, we're
pressing toward the mark. We're pressing
the battle to the gate because Lord, we
know that time is short and we know that
the enemy is stirring up some mess out
here. Oh God, stirring up stuff in this
world, confusing minds and confusing
hearts. Lord, pierce the darkness. We
pray in Jesus name. And may we walk in
the victory that you have spoken over
our lives as the house of David, as a
household of faith, as a seed of Abraham
and heirs according to the promise, as a
righteous Lord God. Hallelujah. In
Christ Jesus, we give you all of the
glory. More than conquerors. Glory to
God. Raised up to sit together in
heavenly places. In Christ Jesus, far
above all principality, power, might,
dominion, and every name that is named,
not only in this world, but also in that
world to come. That we belong unto you,
oh God, purchased by the blood of Jesus.
So Lord, thank you. You you you
purchased the right to work miracles
today. You've purchased it by the blood.
You've given heaven's best. And so Lord,
we thank you. We bless you and we praise
you. And now once again, oh God, as we
sit and prepare our hearts to receive
the word of the living God. Lord, open
our hearts. Open our minds, open our
eyes, touch the lips of your man's
servant. Lord God, what an awesome
channel of blessing. What an awesome
gift you've given to this world. Not
just to Living Manor Church, but to the
world at large. Thank you for Pastor Iva
Meyer. Thank you for Sister Atante
Meyer. Thank you for the Meyers family.
But Lord, thank you for this amazing
gift that you have given us that we
might receive the word from the throne
of grace today. May our hearts be
attentive. May our minds be alert. May
we never be the same. Never again after
this day in
Never.
>> Okay.
Never alone. Never alone.
I am never
alone.
The Lord is my sheer.
He goes before me.
>> Defender behind me.
I won't fail.
The Lord is my
>> The Lord is my sheer.
>> He goes before me.
>> He goes before me. Defender behind me.
>> Defender behind me.
>> I won't fail.
Hallelujah.
Hallelu.
I am not alone.
>> He's my comfort.
always me.
He always guides me
>> through mountains and valleys.
His joy is refreshing.
He restores my soul.
Mercy and mercy and goodness.
Give me assurance.
gives me assurance
>> that I'll see his glory
>> face to face.
>> Hallelujah.
I am not alone.
>> He's my comfort.
Always
hold me close.
Hallelujah.
>> Hallelujah.
I am not alone.
>> He's my
>> He's my God. The way
we go
and goodness and mercy
shall follow me all the days
>> days of my life.
I will dwell
in the house of the Lord
forever
and ever.
Goodness and
>> goodness and mercy.
>> Yes,
>> shall follow me all the days
of my life.
I will dwell
in the house of the Lord
forever
and ever.
Goodness and mercy
shall follow me all the days
of my life.
I will dwell
in the house of the Lord
forever
and ever.
>> Goodness.
>> Goodness and mercy
shall follow me all the days.
>> Days of my life.
I will dwell
in the house of the Lord
forever.
>> And ever
>> forever
>> and ever
forever.
>> Forever
>> and ever.
will dwell.
>> I will dwell in the house of the Lord
forever.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Hallelu.
I am not alone.
He's my
>> He's my
hallelujah.
>> Hallelujah.
>> I am not alone.
You said you'd never leave me.
My comfort
meal.
I am not alone.
>> He my comfort
holds me close.
>> Hallelujah.
Hallelu.
I am not alone.
He's my
>> He's my comfort
hold me.
Amen. Church family, go ahead and put
that one in the chat if you are ready to
get into the word of God today. Um, I
believe the Lord has something very
special for us and uh, we're going to
take a familiar passage of scripture
and uh, by the grace of God, we're going
to pull new flavor and see new light
from this scripture. So I want to invite
you to pray with me uh as
uh we will look at the issue uh today
that I have entitled a place prepared. A
place prepared. Let's pray. Heavenly
Father,
we're asking Lord that you would please
speak to your people yet again. Lord, as
we open the word, I pray that you would
speak to our hearts
and help us, Lord, to understand what it
is that you have to say to your people
today. We pray this in Jesus' name.
Amen. And amen.
A place prepared.
It is a very familiar text to most of
us. In the book of John chapter 14,
beginning with verse one,
the Bible says, "Let not your heart be
troubled. You believe in God, believe
also in me. In my father's house are
many mansions. If it were not so, I
would have told you. I go to prepare a
place for you. And if I go and prepare a
place for you, I will come again
and receive you unto myself that where I
am there you may be also.
Jesus as he is seeking to encourage his
disciples
and not just the disciples in the day
that he was speaking to them but his
disciples from that moment on his
disciples throughout all time. These
words are significant. Let not your
heart be troubled. You believe in God,
believe also in me. In my father's house
are many mansions. How many of you are
looking forward to going to that place
that has many mansions that will house
us throughout all eternity.
Jesus is seeking to encourage us that he
has in fact risen and has gone to a
place that he desires
that we should be with him in that
place.
In the book of Hebrews chapter 8:es 1
and 2,
the Bible says, "Now this is the main
point of the things we are saying. We
have such a high priest who is set at
the right hand of the throne of the
majesty in the heavens, a minister of
the sanctuary and of the true tabernacle
which the Lord pitched and not man. And
so we see that Jesus has in fact
according to scripture gone to that
place called heaven. And there in heaven
he is preparing a place for us. And we
know beloved that if we believe in Bible
prophecy
that the ultimate picture shown in
Revelation 7:9
which reveals a most powerful scene.
Revelation 7:9 after this I beheld and
lo a great multitude which no man could
number of all nations and kindreds and
peoples and tongues stood before the
throne and before the lamb clothed with
white robes and palms in their hands.
They are celebrating
because they are in that place that
Jesus had gone to prepare for them. Once
again, an amen. A one in the chat. If
you desire to be in that place that
Jesus has gone to prepare for us, the
Bible tells us again in John chapter 17
verse 24. He says, "Father, I will that
they also whom thou hast given me, be
with me where I am, that they may behold
my glory which thou hast given me. For
thou loves me before the foundation of
the world." Now, this verse, beloved, is
a verse that that we're going to need to
understand just what Jesus is saying
here within the context of John chapter
14. We typically imagine this verse
as pointing to the time when we will
stand before that throne uh with palms
in our hands and clothed with white
robes saying glory to the lamb uh
salvation to him that siteth on the
throne. And that is in fact true. But
what I want to paint for you today
beloved is a picture that by the grace
of God you will never forget. You see
this verse in John chapter 14, the verse
under consideration, the verse that
tells us, I go to prepare a place for
you. I want you to understand something
about this this verse that you may have
never considered before. And that is
this
that
Jesus
in
in theme
perhaps has spoken these words before.
We don't know if he may have spoken the
words, but we know that the sentiment
was expressed before. Now, you're
saying, "Pastor, what are you talking
about?"
You see what I want you to understand
beloved is that
uh at the beginning of this world
when when when Adam and Eve had fallen
because of sin.
What I want you to understand is that
Jesus
volunteered to come to this world to do
something
on behalf of the father.
You see, Adam and Eve had been an abode
for the spirit of God and for the
presence of God. It had been a place
where where their hearts uh uh were a
dwelling place for God. And when sin
entered, that was no longer the case.
And so I want you to to with your
sanctified
imagination,
imagine Jesus saying almost verbatim
these very words to the father. Behold,
I go to prepare a place for you. Now,
I'm going to ask you all to put a five
in the chat if you are saying to
yourself right now, "Wait a minute,
pastor. Hold on. What did you just say?
What did you just say?" Yes. Yes. Yes.
Beloved, Jesus be at the entrance of sin
in this world, Jesus said to his father,
I will go and prepare a place for you.
Now, you're saying, "Pastor, prove
that." Well, let me prove it to you.
Let's go back to the screen. Let's go
back to the screen. and and and in John
chapter uh 14 uh verse 23, Jesus said
these words. Jesus answered and said
unto him, "If any man love me, he will
keep my words and my father will love
him and we
will come unto him and make our abode
with him."
Did you all catch that?
Did you catch that?
Jesus's mission
when he came to this earth was to make
was to prepare a place
for the father. You all put a seven in
the chat if you if you if it if it's
clicking with you. Wow. Not only did
Jesus say to us, "I'm going to prepare a
place for you." But before that, before
that event, Jesus came to this earth
with a mission of preparing a place for
his father.
Now, now I want you to understand,
beloved, that in the Bible in John
chapter 14, when Jesus said, "In my
father's house are many mansions."
The the Hebrew word, the Greek word that
he used there is the word monet. Monaet
and a bold, a dwelling place. In my
father's house are many dwelling places,
many mansions.
That word Monae is used only o one other
time in scripture and it is found in the
same chapter. Let me read it again.
We're going to put this back up on the
screen. And in John 14:23
again Jesus answered and said unto him,
"If any man love me and will keep my
words and my my father if any man love
me, he will keep my words and my father
will love him and we will come unto him
and make our abode." Monae, the same
word used to describe mansion is now
describing us as his people.
I will come unto him and make our we
will come unto him and make our abode
with him. In other words, you become
God's mansion.
You become God's mansion.
And now beloved, I want you to
understand for maybe for the first time
from a different perspective. When Jesus
says, "In my father's house are many
mansions." What he's saying is, "In my
father's house are many people."
In my father's house are many mansions.
Are y'all following me?
Beloved, that is exciting news.
That is Jesus telling us, listen, my
father is saving many, many people. In
my father's house are many
mansions.
Listen, now we begin to understand why 1
Corinthians 3:16 tells us, "Know you not
that you are the temple of God and that
the spirit of God dwells in you." Are
y'all following me?
Now you can begin to understand when the
Bible says I am crucified with Christ
nevertheless I live yet not I but Christ
liveth in me. Ah
wait a minute. So at the beginning of
time Jesus said to the father I'm going
to prepare a place for you.
A place that you will be able to dwell
in. And that place was the human
sanctuary the human body. Amen.
In a greater con or I should say in a in
a in a different context that place
beloved was the earth.
You see we understand we understand that
ultimately Jesus has come to make this
earth a dwelling place
for his father.
Just as he says to us, I'm going to
heaven to make a dwelling place for you.
Jesus came to this earth to make this
earth a dwelling place for the father.
Okay, we're still building here, guys.
We're building a a a thought here. We're
building a line here, a foundation here
that's going to help us to understand
something mind-blowing.
In order for Jesus
to come and prepare a place for the
father,
according to the book of Hebrews chapter
10:5,
the father prepared a body for Jesus.
Let me read it. When he cometh into the
world, he saith, sacrifice and offering
thou not, but a body thou hast prepared
me. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. So the father
prepares a body for the son so that the
son would come and prepare bodies
for the father to dwell in.
I'm getting too excited over here. Y'all
put a five in the chat if you're
following the thought. Put a five in the
chat if you're understanding. The father
prepared a body for his son
so that the son would come to this world
to prepare not only the earth but
multiple bodies for the father to dwell
in. So again,
when we're reading John 14:es 1-3, what
I want you to understand is that the
context behind that, beloved, the reason
why Jesus can go and prepare a place for
us is because he came to this earth to
prepare a place for his father.
All right, guys.
Here's what I'm going to do. Okay, good.
My slides are back. Revelation 21:3. The
Bible says, "I heard a great voice out
of heaven saying, "Behold, the
tabernacle of God is with men, and he
will dwell with them and shall be his pe
they shall be his people, and God
himself shall be with them and be their
God." I need you to understand that just
as Jesus has prepared a place for us to
go and be with the father. So Jesus came
to this earth to prepare a place for the
father to be with us. Are you
understanding the context? Are you
understanding the context of what we're
building here on John 14 verse 1-3?
Jesus came to this earth to prepare the
earth and the human heart to receive the
father. All right? And so now now within
that context we can understand 2
Corinthians chapter 5 verse 19 which
tells us this that God was in Christ.
Let's get it up on the screen.
All right. So my slides you guys appear
not to be Wow. They appear not to be
functioning. So, we're just going to go
without the slides, unless my slide team
can change a slide for me. 2 Corinth 2
Corinthians chapter 5:1 19. The Bible
says that God was in Christ reconciling
the world to himself, not imputing their
trespasses to them and has committed to
us the word of reconciliation. Jesus
Jesus in go in Christ God was in the
world
or was in Christ reconciling the world
unto himself.
Understand then
that it was in Christ
that the father sent salvation.
one in the chat if you follow me so far.
Now, now we can go back to John chapter
14:es 1-3. And let me read it again. Let
not your heart be troubled. You believe
in God, believe also in me. In my
father's house are many mansions. I want
you to understand the dual meaning of
this. You all, yes, in heaven there are
many mansions that we will ultimately
dwell in. But in another sense, beloved,
God, Jesus is telling us that in his
father's house are many redeemed. In his
father's house are many who have been
saved. You and I are the mansions, the
abolds for the father. If it were not
so, I would have told you, I go to
prepare a place for you. And if I go and
prepare a place for you, I will come
again and receive you unto myself that
where I am, there you may be also. Now,
please understand that in its other in
in the context, we've always understood
this. This is heaven. Jesus has gone to
prepare a place for us. And then he
says, "I will come again and receive you
unto myself that where I am, there you
may be also." Please understand, here is
how the righteous by and large get to
heaven.
According to First Thessalonians 4:3-15,
it says, "But I would not have you to be
ignorant, brethren, concerning them
which are asleep, that you sorrow not
even as others which have no hope. For
if we believe that Jesus died and rose
again, even so them which are asleep in
Jesus will God bring with him. For this
we say unto you by the word of the Lord,
that we which are alive and remain until
the coming of the Lord shall not prevent
them which are asleep. For the Lord
himself shall descend from heaven with a
shout,
with the voice of the archangel, and
with the trump of God, and the dead in
Christ shall rise first. Let me pause
right there. The dead in Christ shall
rise first. I want you to understand
this, beloved, that that when in order
for us to get into that place that Jesus
has prepared for us, there is going to
be a resurrection. It is the
resurrection that ultimately brings us
into that place.
We are looking forward to that day.
that day when we get to be in that place
that Jesus has prepared for us. But I
want to suggest to you beloved that we
may be missing something. And in fact, I
think we are missing something. You see
beloved, in order for us to experience
that place in heaven, there is another
place we must first experience.
And that place, beloved,
uh, let me just read it for you. Let me
just read it for you. In 2 Corinthians
5:17, I want to introduce you to the to
the place that Jesus prepared for us.
Oh, are y'all ready for this? I don't
know if you're ready for this. Because
every time we read John 14, we think
he's going to prepare a place for us.
Oh, that place is heaven and that place
he's away now preparing that place. But
may I suggest to you beloved that in 2
Corinthians 5:1 17 when the Bible says,
"Therefore, if any man be
where
is the place
that we ought to be?"
Y'all put it in the chat for me, please.
Where is the place
that every Christian believer is to be
found?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Beloved, that place is in
Christ.
Could it be possible that when Jesus
said, "I am going to prepare a place for
you." As he is headed to the cross,
Could
it be possible
that the place he has gone to prepared
for us was not only heaven in its
literal s sense but Christ
in the now?
Could it be that in before we get into
the place in heaven, we must get into
the place in Christ.
Let me show you something.
In the book of Exodus 33:7, the Bible
says, "And Moses took the tabernacle and
pitched it without the camp, a far off
from the camp, and called it the
tabernacle of the congregation. And it
came to pass that everyone which sought
the Lord went out to the to the
tabernacle of the congregation which was
without the camp. Here's the ESV
version. Now Moses used to take the tent
and pitch it outside the camp far off
from the camp. And he called it the tent
of meeting. And everyone who sought the
Lord would go out to the tent of meeting
which was outside the camp. So I want
you to understand this beloved. The tent
of meeting.
The tent
Could it be possible, y'all,
that Jesus
is our tent of meeting?
Could it be possible that just as in
Christ,
the place where the father would meet
us,
in Christ is the place where the father
would meet us, he prepared a body. So in
Christ is the place that we meet the
father. In other words, could it be
possible that Jesus Christ is the tent
of meeting?
Not only is he the sanctuary, the
tabernacle itself, but he is also the
tent of the the tabernacle of the
congregation, the tent of meeting. In
other words, in him, father and humanity
meet. What do y'all think?
The place
that he went to prepare.
In fact, I like how in John chapter 2
19, Jesus answered and said unto them,
"Destroy this temple and in three days I
will raise it up." They said, "Then then
said the Jews, 40 and six years we've
been building this temple. Will you rear
it up in three days?" But he spake and
said and but he spake of the temple of
his body. Could it be beloved that Jesus
is the temple, the tabernacle and also
the tabernacle of congregation or the
tent of meeting in which father and
humankind
meet?
Is he the meeting place?
Yes, he is the meeting place, y'all. Ye
Yes, he is the meeting place. Yes, he is
the ladder. I like I want you to
consider Exodus 29:43 where it says
there I will meet with the people of
Israel and it shall be sanctified by my
glory. Beloved, ultimately Jesus is that
meeting place.
And now here's what I want you to
understand
that if Jesus is that meeting place then
beloved when Jesus said in John 14 that
where I am there you may be also it's as
if he's speaking in present tense
not where I am there you one day will be
also no where I am there you may be also
there you may be also when now
listen this is why you guys Colossians 3
1-4 tells us this if you then be risen
with Christ
seek those things which are above where
Christ siteth on the right hand of God
set your affection on things above not
on things on the For you are dead
and your life is hid
with Christ in God.
When Christ who is our life shall
appear, then shall you also appear with
him in glory. You see, there is the
glory then when Jesus appears. But there
is the glory now.
By faith, we are able to see the glory
of Jesus now. How? by being in that
place he has prepared for us. And what
does that require? It requires us to be
born again. Clint, it requires us to be
born again. In Ephesians chapter 2 5 and
6, the Bible says, "Even when we were
dead in sins, has he quickened us
together with Christ, by grace are you
saved, and has raised us up together
and made us sit together in heavenly
places in Christ Jesus."
Are y'all following this?
The text says, "Even while we were yet
his enemies, Christ was coming after
us."
The question then is, how do we get into
this place? This this place called
Christ. Listen to what the text says in
Romans chapter 6:3 and 4. Do you not
know that as many of us as were baptized
into Christ? into Christ. That's the
place that baptism baptism
brings us into a place and that place is
in Christ. That is the meeting place.
This is where we meet God.
Do you not know that as many of us as
were baptized into Christ Jesus were
baptized into his death? Therefore, we
were buried with him through baptism
into death. that just as Christ was
raised from the dead by the glory of the
father, even so we should walk in
newness of life. Yes. Yes. Yes. This is
why Galatians chapter 3 27 tells us,
"For as many of you as were baptized
into Christ have put on Christ."
You see to be baptized,
born of the water, born of the spirit
means
that we are in Christ. The place he went
to prepare for us at the cross. When
Jesus was dying at the cross,
he was preparing a place for us then.
And that place, beloved,
was himself
in his death, burial, and resurrection.
That is the place Jesus prepared for us
so that we could enter that place called
heaven when he comes again the second
time.
Now, beloved, believe it or not, believe
it or not,
everything I just shared just now was
simply setting the stage for what I'm
about to share with you now.
In Romans 5:10,
the Bible says, "For if while we were
God's enemies, we were reconciled to him
through the death of his son, how much
more, having been reconciled, shall we
be saved through his life?" I need you
to understand this. Uh uh Jesus came to
reconcile us while we were yet enemies.
Y'all put a five in the chat if you're
following. While we were yet enemies,
God came looking for us. Who? By how?
Through his son. He prepared a body for
his son so that his son could come into
this world and prepare bodies for him to
dwell in.
And so the son comes into this world and
prepares a body
prepares the son comes into the world in
that prepared body
and he comes with the mission of making
abolds for his father.
So so the way he's going to do that
is through his death, burial and
resurrection.
But beloved, there's something so
special about this death, burial, and
resurrection
because it is only through that death,
burial, and resurrection. How many days
was Jesus dead everybody? How many days?
Three days. It was only through that
experience
that that bodies would be made
abolds for the father.
And we can see that by on the day of
Pentecost when when 3,000 are baptized
in a day. These are living bodies
for Jesus, for God.
Then then listen, we were not just
called to become bodies for or abodess
or mansions
for God. But the Bible then tells us in
1 Peter chapter 2:9, "You are a chosen
people, a royal priest of a holy nation,
God's special possession, that you may
declare the praises of him who called
you out of darkness into his wonderful
light." So the purpose of us being
called by God when we were when we were
once enemies,
God calls us and saves us and then sends
us to be lights for him.
Sends us to declare the praises of him
who called us out of darkness into his
wonderful light.
God saves us so that we can save others.
But before God can do that, before Jesus
can do that, he's got to find us.
He's got to redeem us who were once his
enemies.
And beloved, see what I need you to
understand. Y'all put a y'all
man
y'all put a eight in the chat if you're
like, "Pastor, I'm ready for what's
coming next. I am ready for the
punchline of this entire sermon. I hear
what you're saying and that makes sense.
If we stopped right here, I would get
it. I would walk away saying, "Man, I
understand this now." What a powerful
thought about Jesus being the place
where father and and and lost mankind
meet.
Here it is, y'all. Are you ready?
You see lost mankind, beloved, the man
who is who is
the man who who who God comes looking
for. Reminds me a lot of a man by the
name of Let's just go to the screen now.
The word of the Lord came unto Jonah the
son of Amatei, saying, "Arise, go to
Nineveh, that great city, and cry
against it, for their wickedness is come
up before me." Instead, Jonah headed off
to Tarses to escape from the commission
of the Lord. He traveled to Jopa and
found a merchant ship heading to Tarses.
So he paid the fair and went aboard to
aborted to go with them to Tarses far
away from
the Lord.
Jonah,
God comes to him, but Jonah runs away.
It it's almost like it it it sounds a
lot like Genesis 3:8 where after Adam
and Eve sinned, the Bible says that when
they heard the voice of the Lord God
walking in the garden in the cool of the
day, Adam and his wife hid themselves
from the presence of the Lord God
amongst the trees of the garden. You
see, this is how mankind operates. Ever
since sin entered, it is our natural
bend to run from God. We have become
enemies of God. And so we run from God.
And and God, we don't go looking for
God. God sent his son looking for us.
Yes, God sent his son looking for us.
Now remember in that same chapter,
Genesis chapter 3, uh, verse 19, the
Bible says to Adam, "In the sweat of thy
face shalt thou eat bread till thou
return unto the ground. For out of it
thou was taken. For dust you are, and
unto dust shall you return. In other
words, put differently, for the wages of
sin is death, but the gift of God is
eternal life through Jesus Christ our
Lord. So when Adam and Eve sinned,
their sentence was death. When Adam and
Eve sinned, they went into a natural
flight mode.
The natural tendency was to hide from
God.
And that's a lot like what Jonah is
doing
when we're introduced to him.
And then beloved comes a verse that in
all
my years as a Biblebelieving
Christian
just blew my mind.
Let me show it to you.
It's in Jonah
1 verse 17. Now the Lord
had prepared
a great fish.
Let me read that again.
Now the Lord
had prepared
a great fish.
Beloved, not Satan. Satan didn't prepare
a fish.
The Lord prepared the fish.
Y'all put a nine in the chat for me,
please.
If a fire is beginning to ignite in your
heart, the Lord prepared the place for
Jonah.
The Lord prepared a place for Jonah. A
man running from God. A man saying, "I
am not interested in doing your will."
The Lord, the Lord is the one that
prepared the fish to swallow up Jonah.
Listen to me. For three days and three
nights.
Jesus in John 14 said, "I go to prepare
a place for you."
Yes, faith. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Jesus in John 14, he's about to be
crucified. He's about to be in the belly
of the earth for three days and three
nights. And Jesus says, "I go to prepare
a place for you." And I know as you and
I read this, we're thinking heaven. He's
going to heaven. And and we're not
wrong. We're not wrong. I would just
like to suggest
that part of that preparation was
actually his death, burial, and
resurrection. That tomb in which he
laid, that tomb in which he laid, that
tomb in which he laid for three days and
three nights, could it be possible that
what Jesus is saying is, listen guys, if
you want to get to heaven, you must
first go through that tomb.
You must first have a tomb experience, a
fish experience. You must first have a
cross experience. Now, I get it because
in our minds, we're like, "Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. How can I live
in a place like this?"
What I need you to understand, beloved,
is that the Lord has already prepared a
bornagain
experience for you.
Did y'all hear what I just said?
The Lord has already prepared a
three-day threight experience for you.
And the experience does not necessarily
take three days or three nights. It may
happen in an instant. It may happen in a
day. It may happen in weeks. It may
happen in months. It may happen in
years. But beloved,
God
is the one that has prepared that place
for you
because it is in that place that we are
captured. God's trying to capture us.
Yes. Yes. God is trying to capture us,
beloved. And the place in which he
captures us
is in the tomb of Christ.
It is in the cross of Christ. It is in
the death, burial, and resurrection
experience of Christ. Know ye not that
as many of of you as were baptized into
his death, meaning you went through his
experience, meaning you have gone
through that Jonah experience, that
whalike experience. as many as watch
this y'all.
Where was Jonah
for those three days and three nights?
Y'all ready for the word?
He was hidden.
Jonah
was hidden
in that place.
Let me read it again. Romans 64 verse4.
Therefore, we are buried with him by
baptism into death, that like as Christ
was raised up from the dead by the glory
of the father, even so we also should
walk in newness of life. Colossians 3:3,
for you are dead, and your life is hid
with Christ in God.
Romans 8:1, there is therefore now no
condemnation to them which are
in Christ Jesus, who walk not after the
flesh, but after the spirit. Colossians
2:12, buried with him in baptism, where
wherein also you are risen with him
through the faith of the operation of
God who raised him from the dead.
Colossians or Galatians 3:27.
For as many as you have as have been
baptized into Christ have put on Christ.
Beloved, what I need you to understand
is that the father has all Jesus has
prepared a a bornagain experience for
you and it is up to you to accept it or
reject it.
Understand
that when Jonah is in the belly, when
Jonah is hidden, this is where he meets
God.
Let me show you. Let me show you. Uh uh
uh by the way, when John in John 15:4
and 5, when Jesus says, "Abide in me,
for without me you can do nothing." What
the same abide is the word meno.
Remember abode was monet abide is menow.
It's the same root word. In other words,
he's saying listen.
I am your mansion.
Abide in me.
I know you may think the born again
experience is uncomfortable. I know
you're thinking, "How in the world I'm
going to survive in the belly of a fish,
in the belly of a whale?" But Jonah
survived. That's the miracle, you guys.
Jonah survived
the experience.
God wasn't trying to kill him. God was
trying to save him.
I know you may think, man, it's going to
be uncomfortable if if uh it's going to
be uncomfortable for me to be to have
this born again experience. I'm gonna
have to give up this this, that. I'm g
have to change my my ways about this. It
may be uncomfortable, but beloved, it's
not designed to destroy you. It's
designed to save you.
It is there in the belly of the fish
that Jonah meets
God.
Jonah chapter 2 verse1 Then Jonah prayed
unto the Lord his God out of the fish's
belly and said I cried by reason of mine
affliction unto the Lord and he heard me
out of the belly of hell cried I and
thou heardest my voice for thou has cast
me into the deep in the midst of the sea
and the floods compass me about all thy
billows and thy waves pass me about
Jonah's being baptized y'all that was
Jonah was just being baptized.
He was just being baptized. He was just
having needing a born again experience.
Verse four, then said I, I am cast out
of thy sight. Yet I will look again
toward thy holy temple. The waters
compassed me about, even to the soul.
The depth closed me about. The weeds
were wrapped about my head. I went down
to the bottom of the of the mountain.
The earth with her bars was about me
forever. Yet thou hast brought up my
life from corruption, oh Lord. But do
you understand? This is the born again
experience.
The the the the the going down into the
waters and coming up to be brought up
from corruption. This is the born again
experience. This is the Jonah
experience. And this is why when Jesus
said, "I go to prepare a place for you."
and then goes to the cross.
Beloved, we we lock in on heaven and we
just bypass the cross.
But I need you to understand, beloved,
just like if you were to aim a gun at
something and you you're looking at that
the the the
crossbow,
beloved, in order to hit the mark, you
got to go through the cross.
In order to hit the mark, in order to
get the in order to get to the target,
you have to look through the cross rope,
the crosshairs.
And so it is in Jonah chapter chapter 2
where we see Jonah meeting God. In verse
7, when my soul fainted within me, I
remembered the Lord and my prayer came
in unto thee into thine holy temple.
They that observe lying vanities forsake
their own mercy, but I will sacrifice
unto thee with the voice of
thanksgiving. I will pay that that I
have vowed, salvation of the Lord. And
the Lord spake unto the fish, and it
vomited out Jonah up onto dry land.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Do you understand
that Jesus has prepared a place for us?
He the place he has prepared for us
is designed to capture us, to arrest us,
to introduce us to the father.
And beloved, once we have been
introduced to the father, once we are in
that place, that secret place, that
hidden place where we are protected,
then watch this.
Then we are released
for mission.
Jonah chapter 3 verse 1 and 2. And the
word of the Lord came unto Jonah the
second time, saying, "Arise,
arise,
go unto Nineveh, that great city, and
preach unto it the preaching that I bid
thee." Remember
how I told you that that uh we saw
earlier that that Jesus when he calls us
out of marvelous out of darkness into
his marvelous light,
he desires us to go
and praise his name.
You understand that, right?
So, so it's the gospel commission.
Matthew 28:16. Then the 11 disciples
went away into Galilee into a mountain
where Jesus had appointed them. And when
they saw him, they worshiped him. But
some doubted. And Jesus came and spake
unto them, saying, "All power is given
unto me in heaven and in earth. Go ye
therefore and teach all nations,
baptizing them in the name of the
Father, and of the Son, and of the Holy
Ghost, teaching them to observe all
things whatsoever I command you. And lo,
I am with you always, even unto the end
of the world." It's as if Jesus was the
Jonah who has now been been been been
been spit out of the grave as it were
after three days and three nights. And
now his mission is he tells the
disciples go and preach. Go and teach.
So I want you to understand something
here. Do you remember when um
when Jesus said um
to the disciples, "Come and follow me
and I will make you
fishers
of men." Y'all remember when when Jesus
said that?
Follow me and I will make you fishers of
men. So let me ask you a question. Would
Jesus be the ultimate fisher of men?
Yes, Jesus would be the ultimate fisher
of men. So, so my next question is how
do you what does it mean to be a fisher
of men?
Well, the literal meaning would be that
they're men
uh in the seas
and the goal is to catch these men, is
to arrest these men, is to capture
these men.
Do y'all understand what the fish in the
story of Jonah does?
Men catch fish. Fish don't catch men.
Jesus
as the fisher of men uses his death,
burial, and resurrection as the net as
the fish to capture caught you. All
right.
Oh Lord, I need your grace. I need your
mercy. Forgive me. Forgive me. Forgive
me.
Go.
I'm I'm letting you loose to go and
preach the gospel.
The tomb of Christ in essence becomes
that that that net. The tomb of Christ
in essence becomes that whale that
swallows, that arrests
every individual that must be saved. I'm
catching you. Jesus came as the fish.
Funny, ironically, back in the Old Test,
back in the New Testament time, they
used the fish as a symbol for Jesus.
That's just a historical side note, you
guys. The fish was the symbol for Jesus.
The death, burial, and resurrection of
Christ is the mechanism whereby
men are caught
just like Jonah had been caught?
Has the gospel caught you? Has the
death, burial, and resurrection
experience of Christ caught you and
changed you? Because one of the greatest
evidences that it has caught you and
changed you is that when you are let
loose, you cannot help but to go and
preach. You cannot help but to declare
the marvelous workings of God
to a world that is lost in sin.
And now And now we're almost done. We're
almost done. And now, now you understand
that in Revelation 14 6 and 7, when the
Bible says, "I saw another angel fly in
the midst of heaven, having the
everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that dwell on the earth, and to every
nation, kindred, tongue, and people,
saying with a loud voice, fear God, and
give glory to him, for the hour of his
judgment is come, and worship him that
made the earth, the sea, and the
fountains of waters." It is quite
interesting that when they asked Jonah,
"Who are you?" And he said, "I
I am one who worships the God who made
the earth and the sea, the fountains of
waters."
Beloved, it is a it is a
I want you to understand
that the everlasting gospel
where we are sent to every nation,
kindred, tongue, and people
is very simple.
We're trying to get men caught in the
fish.
We're trying to get men.
We're trying to be fishes of men.
And I want you to understand, beloved,
someone just said, "Hey, my Jonah
represent the complacent Christian."
Absolutely. Yes. But I need you to
understand as well that that Jonah
running away from God is also the very
thing that the wicked do. It's also the
very thing that the lost do. It's also
the very thing that those who want
nothing to God, nothing to do with God
do.
And God so loved the world
that he sent his son.
So beloved, as as we have been released
for ministry, released,
it is to go into all the world,
preaching the everlasting gospel,
preaching a message
that leads people
into that Jonah experience.
into that cross experience
where after they go through that
experience, beloved, they come out,
redeemed
and prepared
to enter into that place that Jesus has
gone to prepare for them. Our closing
verse,
Revelation 7:9. And after this I beheld,
and lo, a great multitude,
which no man could number of all nations
and kindreds and peoples and tongues
stood before the throne and before the
Lamb, clothed with white robes and palms
in their hands. Beloved, please
understand that the only way this was
made possible was when the father
prepared a body for his son so that his
son would come into this world to
prepare bodies for the father.
And the way he does that is by preparing
a place for us
to enter into that 3-day experience,
that death, burial, resurrection
experience.
So that through that Jesus was then able
to say to us, I'm going to prepare a
place for you that is heaven
and my very self so that you can be
hidden in me
and I'm going to take you to meet the
father.
In me the father will meet you and you
will meet
the father.
What a powerful thought.
What a powerful thought. Heavenly Father
sends his son and his son is the place
where man
and God will ultimately meet.
Lord, please make me a mansion for you.
Make me a dwelling place for you.
Lord,
please grant me
that experience
that that death, burial, and
resurrection experience
where I meet you
and I will know that the evidence that I
have met you is that there is now
something burning in my soul
That said, I've I've got to go and share
the goodness of God.
Beloved, there's so many there's so many
other powerful lessons in this story,
but that is a lesson that we need to
lock in on today. Lord,
put grant me that experience.
I've been looking at the place in heaven
and overlooking the place of the cross.
Lord, please help me to understand that
in order to get to the place in heaven,
I must first get to the place in Christ.
If that is your desire, I want you to
put that one in the chat.
If you're listening and you have never
been baptized, and maybe everybody
listening has been baptized, but if
you're listening and you have never been
baptized, you understand the truth, but
you're saying, "Man, I need to do this.
I never knew that that was a place that
Jesus went to prepare for us, and I've
been holding off baptism. I've been, you
know, man, should I do this? I've been
afraid of baptism. What will that mean
for me? Will I be able to survive it?"
Beloved, listen.
Yes. Yes. Trish, pray. Lord, swallow me
up.
swallow me up. If that is your desire
specifically, you're saying, "I want to
be baptized because I've not yet been
baptized." I want you to put a five in
the chat. This is the this this is the
the ones is Lord, help me to have that
experience. The five you the fives
you're saying, "I need to be baptized.
I've not been baptized. I need to be
baptized.
I need to have this experience."
you put that five in the chat and we're
going to have our Bible workers. In
fact, at the end of this message, I'm
going to put up, which is now I'm going
to put up a screen where you can reach
out to our Bible worker um and the Bible
work will connect with you and walk you
through Bible studies to prepare you for
baptism.
I see I see the decisions in the chat. I
pray that that that
the fire of this message will never
leave your soul, will never leave your
heart.
I pray that you will walk away from here
today saying with with an understanding
and that you may never see John 14 1-3
the same way again.
Listen you guys, I see the fives in the
chat. Do not be afraid to be swallowed
up.
Do not be afraid to be swallowed up.
It is an experience that you will never
regret. And and if there's those of you
that need to be rebaptized,
you know the reason between you and the
Lord. Put that five in the chat. Put
that five in the chat. Um we cannot
reach out to you. So, we're asking you
to follow up and reach out to us. Okay,
I'm going to put that last slide up on
the screen so that you can see how to
get a hold of us and then we're going to
pray. So, there is the connect with
living mana. There is the the email for
uh Bible studies. If you have prayer
requests, you'll see where to join there
and to follow us on social media. Let's
pray you guys. Let's pray. Heavenly
Father,
thank you for speaking today.
Lord, thank you for showing us
the place that you have prepared for us
that perhaps we have overlooked,
only locked in on heaven, not realizing,
Lord, that you desire us
to be in heavenly places now.
But to get there, we have to go through
that Jonah experience.
And so, Lord, grant us that experience.
May we truly be born again. And may the
sign be not just that we have been
brought up from corruption, meaning
we've put away old things, but also
that there is a fire in our hearts to
share the message of truth.
Please Lord, may this be our experience.
Fill us Lord with your grace
and may we meet in the meeting place
which is Jesus Christ
is our prayer.
Lord be with those who have made a
decision to be baptized or rebaptized.
Lord lead them to reach out so that we
can walk with them through this process.
And again, Lord, remove the fear of
being swallowed up
in Christ.
May we understand that that experience
will change our lives forever
for the good of our own souls.
In Jesus name we pray. Amen. Amen. We're
going to uh put the link up to join us
on our afterlow discussion. you'll see
it in the YouTube in the uh chat
section. Um please feel free to join us.
Um in fact, we invite you to join us and
we will talk about uh the Sabbath school
the sermon and what you've learned from
them. May God bless you and keep you and
uh we look forward to fellowshipping
with you um on our afterlow. Again, God
bless you and keep you and we'll see you
next Sabbath.
Thank you for joining us today. If this
is your first time worshiping with us,
please check out our website at
livingmana.urch.
We are not just here for Sabbath
service. We have weekly programming too
that covers mental health, physical
health, weekly prayer service, financial
health, and proving the existence of
God. It is our desire that our
programming will continue to bless you.
Please continue to pray for us as we
fulfill God's mission to go into all the
world with the gospel of Jesus Christ.